HDZIMU中文字幕W http://www.hdzimu.com
Wj酆谜叻g
[Internet Enthusiasts]
翻g：blackobsidian  V  Kaxxx llimit
翻g：抓R提尼  燕呢喃  Edward Nygma  Marco
后期：Mike Lee
你I了@啊 是啊
You bought this? Yeah.
F在是我的了 ~哼
And it's ours now. We own this. Mm-hmm.
我凵线@里了 是的吧
I love it. Right?
我就跟你f嘛 你看@惹妒降谋t
What'd I tell you? The fireplace, the built-ins here.
你_定就o你姐妹@
Are you sure you want to give this to your sister?
我花了一整天跑了百公里^戆
Babe, we'd make 100K off this flip all day long.
花心思整理一下h 就@
Trying to make up... This is it?
啊 是的 M戆 你z叫我早硪^就榱
Hey, yeah. Come in. You guys made me ask off an hour early to see
@垃圾
this dump?
我都深有感受不是么 是啊 感X就像
We're all smelling this, right? Yeah, it smells like I'm
我在呼吸新r的排泄物
breathing piss.
]e 不是好地方 我so走
Okay. Not a good fit. So we'll just go.
走吧 拜托 再看看嘛
Come on. Come on. Have a little vision.
看看@法式木T 通向花@
French doors to the garden.
我移走@些椅子 打掉@些
We move the stairs, take these walls down,
搞通向N房的_放空g
create an open concept through the kitchen.
看看@角落里A的染色玻璃 看@Y
There's a gorgeous stained glass here in the corner. The bones are
真棒
really good.
那我何r拿出12000美元硇捱@掉的地基
When's the part we cough up 12 grand to fix the rotted-out foundation?
很明@@些只能搞定一部分 El
Clearly, it's not for them. Let's just flip this one, El.
穿^@l街就有一座公@
There's a park across the street.
砟有了孩子@有座W校
And the schools here are fantastic if you have a baby.
不好意思 什么r候 吉米
When. I'm sorry. I'm sorry, Kimmy.
什么r候要孩子啊
When. When you have a baby.
我就要有孩子了 我的_有了
We're having a baby. We are having a baby.
你知道 @叫宇宙的@F
You see that? That's called manifesting to the universe.
有r候 宇宙X得我把@26000K拿到外面先扔了
Sometimes the universe thinks it's funny if I drop $26,000 on in
比^有趣
vitro first.
哈 你真 我就_玩笑
Oh! You're a dick. I'm kidding.
如果@里真@么棒 你怎么不搬
If this place is so great, why don't you guys move in here?
那他怎么面ξP室和一座公@呢
What are they gonna do with five bedrooms and a park?
很@然他不有
They're obviously never having kids.
看看 他可]有什么情感漏洞要填a
Look at 'em. They don't have any emotional holes to fill.
F在我可要a上
Not that we are doing it to fill...
ef了 Russ 好的
Shut up, Russ. All right.
干嘛@涌粗我 我怎么了
What was that look? What look?
他才f你不有孩子 然后你
He just said you guys were never gonna have kids. Then you did a
很明@是在看我
definite look.
是啊 你什么眼神 你后砘仡^
Yeah, what was the look for? You looked back at me to include me in
看著我
your look.
我]看啊 ^看了
I didn't do a look. Totally did a look.
]有 我想我正在制造一些麻
It wasn't a look. I think we just started some trouble.
能有什么麻 甚至可能要打起砜
There's no trouble. Maybe even a fight.
不打起淼 ]有任何麻 我走吧
There's no fight. There's no trouble. Let's get out of here.
天哪 你不是要孩子了吧
Oh, my God. You guys are gonna have kids now, aren't you?
]啊 Kimmy 我不明白 你f什么
No. What? Kimmy. I don't know. What?
你然有了 因槟o如何都要A我
Of course you are, because you have to win at everything.
然后你要拿你完美的子m打我吧
Then you're gonna throw your perfect uterus in my face too.
你怎么知道我的子m很完美 我甚至]有L
How do you know my uterus is perfect? We've never even tried to have
要小孩
kids.
我都不清楚我是否能言
I don't know if I can get pregnant.
然很完美咯 因槭悄愕穆
Of course it is perfect. It is yours.
嘿吉米 可能有皮革蕊呢
Kimmy. It probably has a leather interior.
e走 吉米 你才砟
Please, Kimmy. You just got here.
Σ黄鹆 彼得 加油吧
Sorry, Petey. Have a good fight.
下次 拉斯
See you later, Russ.
我]o色 你F在就有
I didn't do a look. You're doing a look right now.
并]有 你才是在o色
There's no look. You're doing a look.
好吧 可能我是o了色
All right, maybe I did do a look.
但是到他好大地f 我不有小孩
But just hearing him say it out loud: "We're never having children."
我意思是 真的
I mean, is that true?
我不提@事就是因槊看挝艺fr候你都v
I quit bringing it up because every time I did, you'd say it's not
不是r候
the right time.
我明白 但我是配合不到一起
I know, but we were always so broke.
之后我又得狂 想要重新_始@事
And then we were going crazy trying to get the business started.
我今年已看了五套房了 我想_始uu放下
We've flipped five houses this year, and I'm starting to turn down
O的工作
design work.
我是在想我有一天
I always thought that I'd be a mom someday.
我想我浜昧 真棒 你F在又f浜昧
I think I'm ready. Great. Now you're ready.
然后到孩子十六q 我就是老g父H了
And by the time the kid's 16, I'm gonna be one of those old dads,
就像布R恩 亨德里克森他爸
like Brian Hendrickson's dad.
嘿 爸 怎么影 鹤
Hey, Dad. What's up, Son?
嘿 亨德里克森先生 L
Hey, Mr. Hendrickson, go long!
爸
Dad?
你⑺懒宋依习
You killed my dad!
嘿 爸 醒醒啊
Hey. Hey, Dad. Wake up, wake up. Wake up!
你可]害死亨德里克森桑
You did not kill Mr. Hendrickson.
而且你]那么老
And you're not that old.
我有c子 如果我收B五q的小孩呢
Here's an idea. What if we adopt a five-year-old?
那我36q也能大干一 如何
It'd be like I got cracking when I was 36. How about that?
保持直Y束可以
Keep your end straight, will you?
兄弟 你想多了 ]哪要孩子是好了的
Look, you're overthinking it, bro. None of my kids were planned.
想要孩子了 你搞定它 就@么
Kid shows up, you figure it out. Easy-peasy.
你F在有孩子了 斯D 第四快要
How many kids you got now, Stu? Number four's in the oven right
出生了
Now.
喔哦 Ω逗⒆]什么y的
Wow. Nothing hard about kids.
只要你樗花rg 他就很乖
As long as you spend some time with them, they're cool.
最重要的是和孩子他能和睦共
Most important thing, make sure the moms all get along.
嘿 肉球
Meatball. Hey! Hey, buddy!
想我了
Hey. You miss me?
哦 乖孩子 想我了是吧 我也想你
Oh! That's my boy. You missed me, huh? I missed you too.
真乖
Yeah. You're such a good boy.
嘿 艾莉 我弄砹N房用的毛巾悠
Hey, El. I got the towel samples you wanted for the kitchen.
艾莉 你好
El, you okay?
嘿 怎么了
Hey, what's the matter?
]什么 我就在想你f的IB一
Nothing. I was just thinking about what you said about adopting a
五q小孩
Five-year-old.
我有@么f^ 是啊
I said that? Yeah.
我就是_玩笑 我知道 是有c狂
I was totally... I was joking. I know. It's kind of crazy.
但我真的想了想 寄B中心真的有很多小孩
But it just got me thinking. And there's so many kids in foster care.
而且他常搬戆崛 ]有任何H人
And they're moving from place to place, and they don't have anybody,
@是最我y^的
and it's like the saddest thing I've ever seen.
我找到了@IBC 下周他有介B
I found this adoption agency. They're having an orientation next week.
eo我看@ 我不想看到他的小
No, don't show me that. I don't want to see those little faces.
你想我心 我才工作回砟
You trying to break my heart? I just got home from work.
艾莉 照@些小孩的是一些很特e的人
Ellie, people who take in foster kids are really special.
都是些志愿者 甚至]有
These are the kind of people who volunteer when it's not even a
假期
Holiday.
我可]有假期做志愿者
We don't even volunteer on a holiday.
如果有些 嗯 疾的呢
What if there was, like, a disaster?
那可就像K 那都o所^
What, like a dirty bomb? Whatever.
有那些孩子都到我家T口了
And there's a little kid who ends up on our doorstep.
我就要s走他 只因槲不蛱厥
Are we gonna turn her away because we're not special enough?
那就取Q于 那要考]很多因素的
That would depend. There's a lot of factors that go into it.
我是f 我的食物配o以及可接受的范
I mean, our food rations, the blast radius.
艾莉 你不能在意我S便f的
El, you can't take some offhanded remark I made
然后做出狂地Q定
and turn it into a crazy life decision.
那就是一句玩笑
It was a joke.
是啊
Yeah.
我明白 我只是
I know. I just...
你是Φ 不能逼你去做
You're right. You shouldn't be pushed into something you don't want
你不想做的
to do.
那_是好想法
It was just a nice thought.
晚安
Good night.
好的 我不再_那些玩笑了
All right, I won't make any more jokes like that.
行
All right?
你想看些待修房
You wanna watch a little Fixer Upper?
好吧 我勰 我也勰
Okay, I love you. I love you.
我很空 我的盆友
That's a long fill-up, my friend.
那就是槭裁次蚁肽
Well, that's because I wanted you to come in here.
我隹帐值Q吧 就我跟你 一σ
We're gonna have a karate kicking contest. Me versus you, straight up.
哦 天哪
Oh, God.
@不公平 @真的
It's not fair. That is not...
嘿
Hey.
你可不能再I@些薯片了 太辣了
You can't buy these pita chips anymore. They're way too spicy.
辣的我要流鼻涕了
I'm getting my nose watery and...
F在有超^五十f的寄B和
Over a half million children are currently in foster care.
系y超d了 知道
The system is overloaded, okay?
不能再接收更多孩子了
It doesn't need any more kids.
因此 孩子必得D移 而且生活l件更差
So for a child to be removed, conditions have to be pretty bleak,
通常包括虐待或者被O端忽
usually involving abuse or extreme neglect.
他中的一些更是得憔悴
And some of these kids can often languish in the system,
除非有更多像你@|家庭的⑴c
unless a wonderful family like yours steps up for them.
我一定⑴c 我F在就要ё咭
We'll step up. We'll take one right away.
好O了 我F在就去登 看看我的存
Perfect. Let me go check in back, see what we have in stock.
她然是在_玩笑
She is kidding, of course.
我可]有齑
We do not stock.
你懂的
And you know that.
我可以你W八周的收B家庭n程
But we can take you through the eight-week foster parenting course,
然后你就得到Y格C
and you can get your certification.
然后我就湍c一些寄B孩子配
And then we can pair you with some kids that you can foster
直到你IB成功
until they become adoptable.
但@可不闻 大伙
But it is not gonna be easy, folks.
@些孩子y你的意愿
These kids will test your will,
o你的P系制造毫
put a strain on your relationship,
一不留神就被淘汰
and push buttons you didn't even know you had.
我敢你面f并不是所有人都能做到
I can tell by looking at you that not all y'all are gonna make it.
事上我想你有勇饷@些不快
I actually think this group has got the grit to face some unpleasant..
打_一下 你@就走啦
Excuse me. Y-You guys heading out?
是 好吧 xx 再
Yeah. Okay. Well, thank you. Bye-bye.
好吧 怪我 很明@是的
All right, that one's on me. It absolutely is.
我之前也有^似v 是的
We've gone over this before. We have.
是} ]e
This is a problem. It's a problem.
好的 各位 不如我砹私庀履的名字
Okay, everybody, why don't we learn your names
以及你中意那N型的孩子
and what type of children you're looking for.
哦 你好
Oh, hi.
我是戴安娜 和 迪克 坎
We're Dana and Dirk McCann.
是上帝指引我磉@
And the Lord has guided us here
硎震B一小男孩 女孩也行
to adopt a baby boy... or a girl.
是的 上帝一直在保佑我 嗯哼
Yeah, the big guy, he's blessed us with so much. Mm-hmm.
我就想c孩子分享一家 是的
We'd just like to share it with a child that needs a home. Yeah.
你呢
What about over here?
我是大l @是我妻子杰西
I'm David, and this is my wife, Jessie.
我榱撕⒆右呀努力三年了
And we've been trying to have a baby for three years now.
但不管我怎么做 我就是不能焉
But no matter what we do, I... I can't...
不好意思 能直接到下一位 ]P系
I'm sorry. Can someone else go? It's okay.
好的 我是基特 @是~克
It's okay. Well, I'm Kit and this is Michael.
我也在努力要孩子
We've also been trying to conceive now.
大概奈第一次面_始 Π
Pretty much since the first night we met, right?
]e 我只是不太走\
That is correct. We're just not having any luck.
我想收B一9q左右的孩子
We're looking for a child of any gender
不性eN族
or ethnicity up to nine years old.
你好 我是十月 _斯詹妮斯
Hello. My name is October Ross Jennings.
我想做斡H母H收B一
And I would like to be the single mother
有\犹熨x的青少年
of an athletically gifted teen boy
我能激l他@得全一W金的力
who I can help to reach his full Division One scholarship potential.
最好是美非混血
Preferably African-American.
嗯哼 好的
Mm-hmm. Right?
就像影 弱c 是 真棒
Like The Blind Side. Like the movie. Right? That's great.
H鄣 她不是在_玩笑
Honey, she's not joking.
你是在_玩笑 天哪 Σ黄
A-Are you jo... You're not joking? My God. I'm so sorry.
我以檫在跟著那z基佬的言泄ｉ_玩笑呢
I just thought 'cause of the gay guys' conceiving joke that we were...
我意思是 @是影 弱c 的∏榘
I mean, that is the plot of The Blind Side, so...
我]看^ 所以 拜托 到你了
I've never seen it. So, please, it's your turn. Just do not talk to
e再f我了
me anymore.
嗯 她lj了
Yeah, she's nuts.
Σ黄 我感X很糟
I'm so sorry. I feel terrible. I, uh...
我叫Ellie 你好 @是我老公Pete
So, my name's Ellie. Hi. This is my husband, Pete.
~ 是的 我意思是我不是很了解@
Uh, yeah, I mean, I'm not too sure about any of this.
我是f 我明白 我收B了一只狗 我鬯到
I mean, I get it. We adopted our dog Meatball, and we love him like
l狂 但
crazy, but...
e拿孩子跟狗比 我]有啊
Don't compare kids to dogs. I'm not.
我只是f^去游锸杖菟IB狗是一N
I'm just saying there used to be a stigma about getting a dog from
u辱
the pound,
F在Q作拯救狗狗 而且每人都想要一
but now they're called rescue dogs and everybody wants one.
e再f 收容所 狗狗 了
Don't say "pound," don't say "dog." Just don't.
好的  @并不是
Okay, no, that's not...
只是有c小心Π
It's just all of this is a little scary, right?
可能你Q其檎救孩子 哦 天哪
But maybe if you call them rescue kids... Oh, my God.
泶替收B @更多人能容易接受
...instead of foster kids, more people would be into it
@尤就不在你的研中途x_
and people wouldn't walk out in the middle of your seminar
@δ的目更有椭 彼得e
and it'd be good for your program. Pete! Pete!
我只是f ef了
I'm just saying... Just stop it!
看 各位 @是今天的演v嘉e
Oh, everyone, our guest speaker of the day,
布m_M南德斯和他的家人
Brenda Fernandez and her parents.
他感受你的崆榘
Let's make them feel welcome.
嘿 xx
Hey, thank you.
你好
Hi.
我八qr
So, when I was eight years old,
我和她男朋友Q定
my mom and her boyfriend decided it would be a good idea
在我的旖ㄒ蛔制毒工S
to build a meth lab in our garage.
他逼我樗毒
They made me deliver drugs for them.
他虐待我 有些客人也
They abused me physically, and some of their customers abused me
ξ施性虐待
sexually.
我十一qr 我的煺了
Uh, when I was 11, our garage exploded,
然后我就到@砹
and I was put in the system,
囊地方到另一地方
bounced around from placement to placement.
很快我就十四了
Pretty soon I was 14.
]人想要十q的少年 ^啄旮大了
Nobody wants a teenager, so I'd be aging out in a few years.
事就是一般的孩子都超^了收B年g
The thing is, over half the kids who age out of foster care
最K就是o家可w 染毒 或者]赡昃退懒
end up homeless, addicted, incarcerated, or dead within two years.
到我了 我L_始我作槌赡耆说纳活
That was gonna be me, trying to start my adult life,
但]有家庭愿意Y助我上大W
but with no family to help me pick a college,
假日也o家可回
nobody to come home to on the holidays
榈谝蝗文杏雅腿而哭泣
or cry to when my first boyfriend dumped me for Missy Howard.
但@晌 非常特e的人出F了
But then those two... very special people came along.
而我并]有和善的Υ他
And I didn't make it easy on them.
但o我如何s他走
But no matter how hard I pushed them away,
他是砦顼并我兜L
they were always there with a sack lunch and a ride.
xx你
Thanks, you guys.
到@戆职 有你
Come here, Daddy. You too, Mama.
真棒
That was good.
我橹前P于 弱c 的不言道歉
I am so sorry about the Blind Side comment.
我圻@部影
I love the movie.
再 布m_ 干得不e 很棒 好的 基特 再
Bye, Brenda. Great job. Amazing. All right, Kit, bye.
德克 n上再 大伙涸僖
Dirk. We'll see you in the classes, buddy. Bye, guys. Hey.
如今 你X得我足蛱厥 可能吧
So now you think we're special enough? Maybe we are.
我是f @就是我要做的
I mean, this is what we do.
我看到事情的在因素 搞定它 就象他
We see potential in things, we fix 'em up. Like they did.
他在@孩子 年久失修 的B中找到她
They find this kid in a state of disrepair,
o她漆上新漆 刮去情感屋的
they give her a new coat of paint, scrape off her emotional popcorn
o用y理
ceiling,
安b上叟c自尊的工作_
install some countertops in the form of love or self-esteem, whatever.
我并不是f她像一房子 就如我形容狗
I'm not saying she's a house like the way I said the dog thing in
那
there,
但我想我很m合做@拥氖
but I think we're perfect for this.
但她真的 他不是一幢房子 彼得
But she's really... she's not a house, Pete.
我f了她不是房子 你在我f 然
I just said she's not a house. Are you listening to me? Okay. No,
然在
I am.
我很d^ 你呢
I'm so exci... Are you excited?
我就是有c心
I just get worried
事情真的跟你想的那雍
that you think things are gonna be easier than they actually are.
什么 我]f啊 你f了
What? I do not. You do.
整件事都是你的想法啊 我F在嗨到不行
This whole thing was your idea. Now I'm pumped about it, and you're
而你s不激
not?
不不 我有嗨到 是 看起砜刹幌
No, no, I am pumped. Well, you don't look pumped.
面@右改你生活的重要r刻 你表F得更嗨
A big, life-altering moment like this, you gotta get pumped.
我z可是要去干件狂的大事呢
We're about to do something insane.
你有她f什么 然
Did you hear her speak? Yes.
那是我@子到的最的 我知道哦
It was the greatest thing I've ever heard. I know.
戆 女牛仔 跟著我f
Come on, cowgirl, let me get a "yee-haw." Yee-haw.
不是@  跟我W  咦哈
No, bull. Gimme one. Yee-haw!
大c  狂c  快c  你都快要成橐了
Louder. Crazier. Come on. Come on! You're about to be a mom!
咦哈
Yaaa-hoo!
填馇  艾
Add a balloon, El.
好的  坐下吧
Okay, have a seat.
rg到了
Time's up.
@些是你幻想中的孩子
These are your fantasy kids.
不是你真正的孩子
They are not your real children.
加油  杰西  你快失去她了
Come on, Jessie. You're losing her.
彼得 彼得 彼得  滴答滴答  肌肉男
Pete. Pete, Pete! Ticktock, muscle man.
@不能蜃你奈菇o他的花生u中
That's not gonna bring him back from that peanut butter sandwich you
救回他
fed him.
你真正的孩子非常不一  不能擦除他的
Your real kids will be very different. Can't erase 'em.
做的很好  ~克
Good job, Michael.
好了  十月
All right, October.
我宣布  你的孩子去世了
I'm calling it. Yours is dead.
都在@了
All there?
是r候把@些想法抹除了
Time to erase these ideals right now.
R上就好
Almost done.
R上就好了  好的  好的
Almost done. Okay. Okay.
xx你
Thank you. Thank you.
好了  所有人  我想你O想一下
All right, everybody, I want you all to imagine
(恭喜你@些被bC出的^父^母)
你得到了一新的舒服的工作
you got this plush new job.
他o你一又大又好的k公室
They give you a nice big office.
有健身房和冷鏊崮C就在
There's a gym and a frozen yogurt machine right there in the break
休息室
room.
我O了冷鏊崮
I love frozen yogurt.
但是刃纳钐  你知道自己不蛸Y格
But deep down, you know you're not qualified.
你心里深知
In your heart of hearts,
你自己不蚝  以后被_除
you know you're not good enough and you are going to get fired.
就像你之前三次被_除一
The same way you got fired from your last three jobs.
你也有可能主愚o去拿回一些掌控
And you might quit just to get some control back.
你甚至有可能打翻那死的冷鏊崮C
Hell, you might even tip over that damn yogurt machine
然后不要的哪抢镒叱鋈
and walk your ass right on out of there.
澄清一下
Just to clarify,
P不是在倡г诠ぷ鞯牡胤礁闫
Karen is not advocating vandalism in the workplace.
重c在于  刃母惺苁且拥
The point is, that it's the same...
τ谝被冷落的孩子碚f
for a displaced child...
他知道你其并不想要他
who knows... that you don't want her.
除了槭去工作
Except instead of grieving...
而悲
the loss of a job,
她在失去和所有人和事
she's losing her connection
的系
with everything and everyone.
但仍有一系
But the one connection
存在
that can remain
就是同胞兄妹之g的系
is between siblings.
有rτ谕胞兄妹碚f更容易去m
Sometimes it's easier for sibs to adjust
因樗不是孤一人的v了生活中的一切
because they're not going through it all alone.
你也S考]去升到同胞兄妹的e
You might want to consider upgrading to a sibling set.
德克  你考]同胞兄妹
Dirk? Would you consider siblings?
@大家伙也S笑出
The big guy might smile on that.
我要去
Um, w-we'd have to...
我要去祈\    H鄣  ]e
We'd pray on that. Right, honey. Yeah.
去祈\  那大家伙不o你超^你所能
Pray on it. The big guy wouldn't give you any more than you can
掌控的
handle.
我不敢同
I beg to differ.
彼得  艾利  你好啊
Pete. Ellie. Hey.
你砹  你好
You made it. Hi.
砗到  然后е@表格
Just sign in, and take this form with you
下任何你到的你可能感d趣的孩子的名字
and write down the name of any kid you meet you might be interested
字幕
in.
真的  就是@么做的
Really? That's how this works?
]e  @是有c像I孩子
Yeah, it can feel a little like shopping for kids.
@有些混y  我知道  但是家弄了@些
It's messed up, I know, but the county puts these on
因樗能快速的配Φ胶芏嗪⒆雍透改
because they can match a lot of kids and parents quickly.
天  看看那的大孩子
God, look at the big kids over there.
我心都碎了
Breaks my heart.
大多等η嗌倌瓴桓信d趣
Most folks want nothing to do with teenagers.
然  除非你J槟可以o大c的孩子出地方
Of course, if you two thought you could make room for an older child..
不  我的意思是  我  天啊
Um, I mean... I... Oh, God.
Σ黄  都是我的不好  Σ黄
I'm so sor... We... We're terrible people. I'm sorry.
不是你的e  F在M去吧  o自己找家  去吧
You're not terrible. Now get on in there and find you a family. Go on.
天啊  @感X好奇怪
God, it's so weird.
正常情r下  你走出去  和公@鹊娜我庖孩子聊聊天
Normally, you go out and chat up some random kid in a park and you're
你被逮捕的
gonna get arrested.
我F在就@么做  我明白你的想法
Now we're just supposed to? I know.
@小家伙就他自己一人待著  想去打招呼
This little guy's all by himself. You want to go say hi?
是的  ]e
Yeah. Okay.
打_一下  Σ黄  非常抱歉  此孩被占  等下  Σ黄
Excuse me. Sorry. So sorry. Occupied. Hey! Sorry.
被我占了  不好意思
Occupied! Sorry!
我只是去Ic|西  你_c  行
We just went to get treats. So, yeah, just back it up. Okay?
看啊  我砹它c零食    R卡斯  磉@
Hey, look, we got some snacks. Come on, Lucas, right over here.
打_一下  注意
Hey. Excuse me! Heads up!
]事了  xx
Never mind. Thanks.
你拿住它  然后L把它扔到他嘴里
You just take it and try to throw it into his mouth.
真的  你想碓一下
Really. You want to have a go?
好吧
Oh.
很高d到你
Nice to meet you.
抓到了  很好  把她н^
Get it? Oh, yeah. Bring her in!
等下  你要等著到你  兄弟
Hey. You gotta wait for your turn, buddy.
很抱歉  ]事  我去e的地方吧
I'm sorry. Let's... Let's just go. Let's just go.
彼得  艾莉
Pete. Ellie.
最近怎么  你好
How's it going? Hey.
好吧  @一c奇怪
Yeah, well... it's a little weird.
是的  @些事情是有c擂
Yeah, these things can be kind of awkward.
但是你遇任何感d趣的孩子了
But did you meet any kids that you're curious about?
我碰一自己一人坐著的小女孩
We met one little girl who was sitting all by herself.
很可  有c认  好像在周Q起了隔x
Very sweet, a little guarded. Kind of had a little wall around her.
τ谕g人碚f她也很矮小  有可能是烟r酒或者
Really small for her age too. Maybe a fetal alcohol thing or
e的什么原因
something.
我看她  就在那
I saw her... Oh, right there.
那有悲的扎著p子的小女孩
The little sad-looking one with pigtails
看起硐袷谴蟀胼子被一散崞魇`了
who seems like she's been chained to a radiator half her life.
呃  那是我女  那散崞骱⒆
Uh, that's my daughter. The radiator kid?
什么
What?
是的  那是我女
Yeah. That's my daughter.
不好意思
I'm so sorry.
你不必抱歉  我很樗傲
You don't have to be sorry. I'm really proud of her.
她不和e人坐一起的原因是因樗有了一家庭
The reason she's sitting away from others is because she has a family,
一很幸福的家庭
a very happy family.
而且我言械r候也]碰一滴酒  我也]有一
And I didn't drink a drop when I was pregnant. Nor do I have a
散崞
radiator.
然  你感到傲  我是的
Of course. You should be really proud. I am.
我受不了看著那些了  不管了  我要去那了
I'm sick of looking at that. To hell with it. I'm going over there.
彼得  等下  彼得
Pete. Hey, Pete.
彼得  你在做什么  去那看看他
Pete, what are you doing? Look at them over there.
他就像粘^屎一  所有人都避_他  我只是想
Everybody's avoiding them like they're dipped in shit. I'm just gonna
去打招呼
go say hi.
好吧  等下  彼得  等一下
Yeah, okay... Hey, Pete, Pete, just wait.
我知道  我感X@很糟糕  但是他是青少年  明白
I know. I think it's awful. But they're teenagers, okay?
他吸毒  他打wC
They use drugs, and they masturbate,
他在油管W站上看e人玩子游
and they watch people playing video games on YouTube.
我]槟切┳龊  那我槭裁醋龊
We're not equipped for that. What do we have to be equipped for?
我只是想去打招呼  我知道  我不J槲那么做
I'm just going to say hello. I know. I don't think we should do that.
打_一下  你好  你好
Excuse me? Hi. Hey. Hi.
你好啊
Hi!
只是想告V你一下  我都能的
Just FYI, we can all hear you.
什么  粘^屎
Hmm? "Dipped in shit."
打wC  @些
"Masturbate," so forth.
我很感x@些P心  但]必要f的@么
Uh, we appreciate the concern, but there's no need to go all pity
狂
crazy.
我知道@是怎么淼
We know how this works.
去e的地方吧  ]事的
So just go on. It's okay.
去和那些小孩子混在一起  不要多想  好
Go mingle with the kiddies and don't give it another thought, okay?
^得愉快  xx  再
Have a good day, folks. Thanks. Bye-bye.
那么  你出去  是o自己找了青少年
So, you two went out and found yourself a teenager after all, huh?
我只了酌腌  但是她留下了一很好的印象
We only met her for a second. But she made a real impression.
是的  是一很好的孩子
Oh, yeah. Lizzy's such a great kid.
她在W校表F很好  磉@
She does really well in school. Come on back.
四年前她十一q的r候就碚疹所了
She came into care four years ago when she was 11.
花了很久去裾f她接受安置在一寄B家庭
Took a lot to convince her to accept placement in an adoptive home.
她  把房子弄起火了  在裂掉的管子旁倒了
Her mother... Set the house on fire, passed out with a crack pipe.
我想f的是  在我f出事之前
What I was gonna say... Before I told it like it is?
在你打辔抑前
Before you jumped on in there,
她@啄碓S下了很多承Z
is that her mother's made a lot of promises over the years
但]有⑺M行到底
and never seems to follow through with them.
她F在在哪里
Where's her mom now?
也S在院子里穿著B衣u著香
Probably in an orange jumpsuit selling smokes in the yard.
我保C那并不蚀_
I'm sure that's not accurate.
最后lF的就在Oz里接受判Q
Huh. Turns out Lizzy's mom is finishing a sentence in county jail.
lf^什么  lf^
Who called it, huh? Who said it?
你f^  好吧
You did. Yeah.
看起硭]有砗退的孩子重聚
Looks like she's never pursued reunification
也在超^赡]有系^她的孩子
or contacted her kids in over two years,
那么  好吧  她差不多就是o足p重的事
so, yeah, she's pretty much a nonissue.
@糟糕O了  那她爸爸呢
That's terrible. What about the father?
你在f什么呢  爸爸
What are you talking about, "father"?
你在o我表演喜  彼得
What, are you doing comedy for us now, Pete?
P  我有很多站出淼陌职
Karen, we've had plenty of fathers who have stepped up,
但是在@里  任何生父都]有名字
but in this case, no ID's on any birth fathers.
著  的是w系下的a物
Look, Lizzy's mom is a product of the system
她]W^怎么照好自己  更不要f三
and she never learned to properly care for herself, much less three
孩子了
kids.
三  三孩子  什么
Three? Three kids? Oh. What?
是的  三
Yeah, three.
是的    一次生下的
Yeah, Lizzy... At once?
是的  和她小c的同胞兄妹阮和塔是一起淼
Yeah, Lizzy comes with two younger siblings, Juan and Lita.
等等  那我  要I三孩子
Wait, wait. So we would have... three children?
不  吧  也S  但是我不可能能IB三的
No. Two, maybe, but there's no way we can do three.
我的意思是  我曾想去看看  天啊
I mean, we wanted to meet... Oh, my gosh.
槭裁醋我看@  你是混蛋
Why would you show us that? You're an asshole.
你槭裁匆我看@  他@么可  @么做不
Why would you even show that? They're so cute. That's wrong.
J真  我不掩@件事  好
Listen, we're not gonna sugarcoat it, okay?
塔是  野U吵[的孩子
Lita is a... a wild, rowdy kid,
阮有c脆弱  感情上有c敏感
and Juan can be fragile and a little emotional,
意志力很  她不p易信任他人
and Lizzy is strong-willed and she won't trust easily.
@你能怪她  好吧  但是著
God, can you blame her? Well, but listen.
我一般不建h@次配  要不是我相信
We wouldn't recommend this match if we didn't believe
通^一些造和感情
that with some structure and love
@三孩子也S`放出花  明白
these... these kids could blossom, right?
是的  并且我希望能蜃他[F在的寄B
Yeah, and we're hoping to get them out of their current foster
情r
placement.
R斯基一家也S失去@票  P  ef了
The Muskies might lose that meal ticket. Karen, please.
我大多档募酿B父母是很棒的很有同情心的人
Most of our foster parents are really terrific, caring people.
但_也有些人是榱顺诙做@些
And, yes, there are people who do it just for the paycheck.
但R斯基一家并不是虐待或者有害的
But the Muskies are not abusive or evil.
只是有一c  近HY婚
Just maybe a little... Inbred.
P  ]有C表明  你^他了
Karen, there is no evidence to... You've seen 'em.
我l誓他看起硐裥置  我分辨不出他
I swear they look like brother and sister. I can't tell them apart.
不管怎么f  我很芬獍才乓探L
In any case, I'd love to set up a visitation,
除非你有e的]
unless you have any other concerns.
只是一探L  那么
It's just a visitation. So...
只不^  @真的]}
I-I-It's just... Is it a problem...
你知道的  整白色救世主@件事
You know, the whole white savior thing?
就像阿凡_那件事  阿凡_
Like the Avatar thing. Avatar?
你知道{色的家伙是怎么]k法敉四切聿傻V的人
You know how the blue guys couldn't fight off the unobtanium guys
直到白色的人出F了并窝b成了一{色的人
until the white guy showed up and pretended to be a blue guy?
我想f的是  白w色的夫D接{著拉丁小孩
All I'm saying is, white-bread couple taking in little Latin kids.
人不X得我不@么做
Are people gonna think we shouldn't be doing that?
你知道  我重新把那些小孩放回去
You know what? We'll go ahead and toss these kids back into the system
然后o你下  HIB白w色小孩
and I'll just jot you down for "whites only."
不不不  我不是f  等下  不是  @不是
Come on. I didn't mean... Hey! No, that's not...
e下  HIB白w色小孩  @不是他的意思  @不是
Don't write "whites only." That's not what he meant. That's not
焊不是我的意思
at all what I meant.
彼得  我感激你的文化敏感
Pete, I appreciate your cultural sensitivity,
但是我@里收{了各Nw色的小孩
but we have every color of kid in the system.
我也有各Nw色的父母  每Nw色
And we have every color of parent. Every color.
只是不蚨  -父母盗坎蚨
Just not nearly enough. Not nearly enough parents.
著
And listen.
你受到一些奇怪的眼光
You're gonna get some funny looks.
人也f些蠢
And people are gonna say some stupid shit.
但是如果你真的喜g@些需要爸爸的孩子
But if you're willing to love these kids who need a mom and dad,
而有人Υ擞挟h
and somebody has a problem with that,
你只需要他收B了多少的孩子
you just ask 'em how many goddamn kids they've adopted.
]e  f得
Exactly. Hell.
我只是想f一下阿凡_  F在我f完了  我]}
I just wanted to have the Avatar talk. Now we did, so I'm good.
好  棒O了
Oh, fantastic.
你浜萌ヒ孩子了  三孩子
You ready to meet three kids? Three kids?
是的  那好  我安排一下的
Yeah. All right. We'll set it up.
你好  ^得怎么
Hey. How's it going?
很好  ^得很好
Uh, good. It's going really good.
我是彼得和艾莉  我知道  M戆
Pete and Ellie. Yeah, we know. Come on in.
希望你能和那孩子^得  她J樗比所有人都好
Good luck with that one. She thinks she's better than everybody.
是啊  另外就在后面e逛
Yeah. The other two are jackassing around out back.
我去商店
We'll be in the shop.
你好  瓦格{夫D  你好
Hey, uh, Mr. And Mrs. Wagner. How are you?
叫我彼得和艾莉就好
Oh, uh, Ellie and Pete.
你不用叫我瓦格{夫D  不  ]事  很芬
You don't have to call us the Wagners. No, please. Good to...
Σ黄  他  ]事
Um, sorry about them. They're... Oh, please.
他只是有c  像兄弟姐妹
They just seem a little... Like brother and sister?
管好你的嘴  我不是H戚P系
Pipe down with that crap. We are not friggin' related.
天⒌挠H訇P系
Friggin' related.
我真的很想念他的
I'm really gonna miss them.
前提是  如果你  不不不  天啊
That is, if you... No. Please. Oh, my goodness.
我第一次面r你o我留下了很好的印象
You made such a good impression on us when we met you,
我想多了解你一c
we wanted to get to know you a bit more.
是的  你的兄弟姐妹
Yes! Meet your brother and sister.
他就在外面  如果你想跟著我  是的
They're right outside, if you guys wanna follow me. Yes! Yes.
阮  塔
Juan. Lita.
我想你彼得和艾莉
I want you guys to meet Pete and Ellie.
你好  嘿  孩子
Hi. Hey, guys.
我F在就要住在你家了
Are we gonna go stay at your house now?
我^你姐姐  她很棒
Well, we met your sister, and she's so awesome.
是的  她很酷  她正告V我P于你的事
Yeah, she's really cool. She was telling us about you guys.
想和我一起去餐d
Want to play restaurant with me?
是的  我很芬
Yeah, I would love to.
你的餐^在哪里  就在那
Where's your restaurant? Right over there.
你的洋娃娃叫什么名字  她的名字叫薯片
And what's your doll's name? Her name is Potato Chips.
我喜g薯l  薯l是我最喜g的
I love potato chips. Potato chips are my favorite.
很好的投球
Nice one.
我能快船  我更喜g湖人
Can we be the Clippers? I'm more of a Lakers fan.
哦  Σ黄  你不需要fΣ黄鸬  ]事的
Oh, uh, sorry. You don't have to say sorry. That's okay.
我可以快船  好的
We can be the Clippers. O-Okay.
我要投球了  你去诎  好的  ]}
I'm gonna shoot, you crash the boards. Yeah. Sure.
你是故意的  什么
You did it on purpose! What?
你糁形揖鸵槲蚁g快船
You hit me 'cause I like the Clippers.
快船很棒啊  我喜g快船  你在_玩笑吧
The Clippers are awesome. We love the Clippers. Are you kidding me?
[了布雷克 格里芬真是太明了  那是一P很好的交易
It was so smart to get rid of Blake Griffin. That was a great trade
τ谇蜿碚f
for them.
我O了快船  我都不λ感到
We're obsessed with the Clippers. I can't get enough of them.
他太棒了  好吧
They're amazing. Okay.
我可以玩玩捉迷藏  你_定  你流了很多血
Can we play hide and seek? You sure? You lost a lot of blood.
我喜g捉迷藏  好吧  但只有我  ]有女孩
I love hide and seek. Okay, but just us. No girls.
哦 好吧
Oh. Sure.
有c老套  但]P系
It's not that progressive, but no problem.
塔 我去玩^家家吧  好
Lita, should we go play restaurants? Yeah.
你戆  我聿啬岛
You're it. I'll hide and you count. Okay?
你_定你]事   我]事
You sure you're okay? Yeah.
快c  _始蛋  档20   好的
Go on, count. Count to 20. All right, buddy.
天啊
Oh, my God.
你最好e在餐^我下不砼_
You better not embarrass me at the restaurant.
薯l今天特e  呐孩
Potato Chips has been bad today. Bad girl!
牡  牡  牡
Bad, bad, bad!
e嘴  你U物
Don't talk back, you little beaner!
哦 ~  我X得
Oh! Uh... I don't think that's...
你知道  她是碾上W淼倪@些|西
You know what? She picks up that stuff off the TV.
是的  e@么看我
Yeah. Oh, don't give me the look.
不能@诱f她的     不用你教我怎么ξ业暮⒆
Let's not call her bad names. Don't tell me how to treat my kid!
你是X得自己做的比我好是
You think you're better than me, huh?
彼得  如果你不想要孩子的
Pete, if you don't want the kids,
我不逼你的
I'm not gonna push you into it.
好吧
All right, look.
我告V你吧
I'm gonna be honest with you, all right?
我也不知道  我只是J楫遇我的孩子的r候
I don't know, I just thought when we met our kids
就像冥冥之中有感一 你明白
that it would be like this cosmic connection, you know?
就是看一眼就知道是我的孩子  就像我初一情一
Like just take one look at them and just know, like when you and me met
是啊  完全同意
Yeah. Totally.
哇 哇 哇 你早就@么J榈
Whoa. Whoa, whoa, whoa. What, you didn't just know?
-嗯  哦  天哪
Hmm? Oh, my gosh.
怎么了  你到我f什么了  你不是才@酉氲
What? You heard what I said. You didn't just know?
不是啊 我很感d趣  但是 你知道的 我比^慎
No, I was interested, but, you know, I'm more cautious than you are.
真的  真的  你什么r候@么想的
Really? Wow. How long before you just knew?
月前吧
A couple of months.
月前  月
A couple of months? How many months?
差不多 四
Like, four...
四月  十四月前
Four? ...teen.
十四月前  天
Fourteen? Oh, my God!
我]Y婚前我就知道了好  @就是}所在
I knew before we got married, okay? That's the point.
在收B他@件事情上我可]Cm一年
We don't have a year-long engagement on this thing.
如果我同意的  他下周就搬M
If we say "yes," they're in our house next week.
你感X到冥冥之中的系了
Did you feel a cosmic connection?
]有  我]有感X到
No, I didn't feel a cosmic connection.
我X得我  我像是在oe人的孩子保姆
I felt like I was... I felt like I was babysitting other people's kids
我同意
I agree.
同意什么  同意你f的
With what? With you.
同意我想要孩子是不想要孩子
With me wanting the kids or not wanting the kids?
你f的都同意   @算什么回答
Whatever you want. That's not an answer.
那o我14月我考]一下  怎么
Then just give me 14 months to think about it. How 'bout that? Come on
嗨
Hi!
@可不是家常便
It's not a potluck.
好了
All righty.
H鄣  臀曳乓幌逻@ 多x
Honey, put those down for me. Thank you.
好了  各位
All right, come on, everybody.
H鄣  入座了 天
Honey, come on. Jeez.
好了  各位  手
All right, everybody, hands.
手 手 手  xx
Hands, hands, hands. Thank you.
]上眼睛
Eyes closed.
我很感激有可鄣O子O女
I'm thankful for my beautiful grandchildren,
包括那非常幸\的孩子
including the... the very lucky kids
他即⒈很棒的父母IB
that are soon to be adopted by two wonderful parents.
我也X得很感激
I'm really thankful for that too.
@是非常值得鼓畹  做的很好
That is really inspiring stuff, you guys. Well done.
其  P于IB的事  我
Yeah, about that. Actually, we...
我Q定r不IB了
Yeah, we've decided together not to move forward with the foster thing
是的  我意R到我]有好好的考]清楚  所以
Yeah, we just realized we hadn't thought it through properly, so...
天  太棒了
Yeah! Jesus Christ. This is great news.
我是f  我都是支持你的  但是
I mean, we were all being supportive to your faces, but...
我都X得你了才IB孩子
Yeah. We all thought you were out of your minds.
我什么都]f^ 但是我真的很高d到你f不IB了
I never said anything, but I'm thankful to hear this.
啥  槭裁
What? Why?
艾莉  e@  我恐手呢   e e e
Ellie, let's not. We're holding hands. No, no, no, no.
我很感激你槭裁@件事有意
I would be thankful to know why you all have a problem with this.
嘿 我Υ送耆]意  我X得很明智
Hey, I never had a problem with it. I think it's smart.
不用言]有荷蒙失{]有情w失控就有孩子
Have a couple kids without the pregnancy and the hormones and the rage
]嘴   艾莉
Stop talking. Ellie.
我是f我很感激
All I'm saying is that we're thankful
你和彼得v槿烁改
that you and Peter are gonna experience
疼勰H生的可鄣暮⒆ 而不是
having the love of your own beautiful children rather than...
而不是什么    你f出  我碚f
Rather than what, Jan? Just spit it out. Hell, I'll say it.
而不是去收B什么
Rather than just rolling the dice
罪犯或者a君子的孩子
with the offspring of some criminal or drug addict.
f  我很心我孩子的安全
To be honest, we were worried about our real kids' safety...
啥  孩子一K出去玩  f一你IB的孩子是
What? ...were they to hang out with your kids, if they're...
次品
Damaged goods?
我L@么大  也有很多人J槲沂谴纹
When I was growing up, a lot of people thought I was damaged goods too
彼得  我不是在f你的
Pete, we're not talking about you, man.
我f的是那些有^性}_的孩子
We're talking about crack babies and kids who have been sexually harassed.
性}_    你什么意思  他的父母使他生聿豢
"Sexually harassed"? What do you mean? Their parents made lewd comments?
你知道我在f什么  自作明      _你的狗眼吧
You know what I mean, wiseass. Open your stupid eyes.
大家什么r候都_眼了  吉米 有所有在座的各位
How long have everyone's eyes been open? Kimmy, you of all people.
如果你不能生孩子呢 e把@N假O放在所有人身上
What if you can't have a baby? Do not put that out into the universe, please.
如果呢  你怎么k
What if you can't? What are you gonna do?
你要是再因楹⒆拥氖卤票
If you don't quit being so nuts about this baby thing,
我l誓 我下午就言
I swear to God, I'm gonna get pregnant again this afternoon
就榱盒哪
just to spite you.
你知道我能做到的  真的
And you know I can do it. Really?
假的  哦
No. Oh.
如果我的立龈大家不同  那很抱歉
I'm sorry if we're not as politically correct as you guys,
但是孩子身上必流著我的血
but our baby has to be our blood.
是的 必是 我的天 “我的血”
Yes! Absolutely! Oh, my God. "Our blood."
@血  在@的@血  那是什么意思
This blood? This blood right here? What's that supposed to mean?
杰瑞  你f呢   有吃我已很感激了  拉斯
Jerry, what do you think about this? I'd be thankful if we could eat, Russ.
你花了三十分家大事
You just spent 30 minutes talking about the deep state.
自己家的事你不管了
You don't have an opinion on your own family?
不P我的事 多x 老爸
None of my business. Thank you, Daddy.
我想告V你成千上f的孩子
I would like you all to know that thousands of children
根本]有家人一K^感恩
are spending Thanksgiving without any family at all.
但是F在我有cw慕他了  我知道你畚
And right now I kind of envy them. But I know you guys love me.
我知道我有地方吃火u  我很感激
I know that I have a place to go to eat turkey and be thankful.
但是很多孩子]有
But a lot of kids don't have that.
@根本不是他的e 有他不是次品
And it's not their fault! And they're not damaged goods!
所以我收回我f的 我是收B的
So forget what I said before. It is back on!
如果你]意的 H鄣   咦哈
If that's okay with you, honey. Yee-haw, baby.
咦哈  我就是要收B@些孩子
Yee-haw. We're gonna adopt a whole shitwhack of kids.
l他有意可以L蛋了  感激不M
And I am thankful that whoever has a problem with it can fuck right off
阿T  阿T
Amen. Amen.
好了 又一感恩
Well, there goes another Thanksgiving.
你太酷了
You're crazy.
嗨 H鄣 我回砹
Hi, honey. Here we are.
M砜纯
Come in, look around.
@是肉球
This is Meatball.
圣Q
A Christmas tree?
@意味著圣Q老人
Does that mean Santa comes here?
是啊 每年都  耶
Yeah, every year. Yay!
所以  你很有X  有X 不
So, you guys are rich. What? Ri... No.
我不是很有X的  就好
We're not rich. I mean, we're doing okay.
搬淼r候@里是垃圾
Well... When we got this house, it was a dump.
我翻新了@房子  艾莉全程O
That's what we do. We renovate houses. Ellie did all the design work.
H上  所有|西都是呐f集市和跳瘙市鲑I淼
Actually, everything is from swap meets and flea markets,
一c都不F
and it's not that expensive at all.
那是水晶 不好意思 天    Σ黄Σ黄
That's crystal! Sorry. Oh, my God. I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
很抱歉  我不把@放在外面的
I'm so sorry. Uh, I shouldn't have left this out.
你想去看看自己的房g 走吧 我去看看你的房g
You guys want to see your rooms? Come on. Let's go check out your room
快看啊 小床有小兔子  你X得怎么
Lookit! A bed and a bunny! What do you think?
我喜g@小兔子因樗穿著裙子
I love the bunny 'cause she has a skirt.
@些玩具是l的  @些都是你的
Whose toys are these? They're yours to share.
是的
Yeah.
犯
Lego!
我能把我的熊放那幔
Can I put my bears in there?
然了 然可以
Sure. Of course.
哇  你有好多泰迪熊啊  @些是法庭熊
Wow, you have a lot of teddy bears. These are just court bears.
我去一次家庭法庭就有一熊
They get one every time we go to family court.
你能拖挛  可以啊
Can you help me? Yeah.
哇 哇 哇  你看@ 塔
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa! Look at this, Lita.
我你去你的房g吧
Lizzy, want me to show you your room?
好啊  就在@
Okay. Yeah. It's just here.
很抱歉你用@些塑料袋b行李
I'm so sorry you have to carry all your stuff in these awful bags.
如果我知道的 不不不 ]P系的
If we knew... No, no, it's cool.
有趣的是 H上可以以此判嗍遣皇且IB的孩子
Fun fact: that's actually how you can spot a foster kid.
@N孩子一子都е大袋子
The kid carrying her whole life in a Hefty bag.
@是IB圈的玩笑
It's a foster joke.
在家你就S意c
Well, make yourself at home.
是啊  @是你的地P  你想怎么佣伎梢缘
Yeah, this is your place. You can do whatever you want with it.
想在ι腺N海  涂色
Do you wanna put posters on the wall, you wanna paint it?
是啊  @我可以兔  20分搞定
Yeah. Come on, This is what we do. We can knock that out in 20 minutes.
去下面的五金店  挑你喜g的色 你f呢
We can run down to the hardware store, pick any color you like. What do you say?
任何色都可以  你自己挑
Any color. Just pick a color.
你喜g什么色   什么色都可以的
what color do you like?   Any color you want
你想怎佣伎梢
Anthing you want
你挑色  我刷上  你好像挺喜gG色的
You pick a color, we're doing it. You'd look great in green.
天
Yeah.
X得怎么
What do you think?
哇  ~  有c像最黑的那Nr石的色
Wow, uh, it's, yeah, darkest of the black tones.
是的 就是她x的色  -深睾  是
Yeah, that's what she picked. Dark Kettle Black, huh?
我喜g  酷懒
I like it. It's really... dope.
我得去渫盹了  去吧
I'm gonna get dinner started. Okay.
她不喜g@色  我X得她超圻@色
She doesn't like it. I think she loves it.
好吧 你比我了解她
Well, you know her better than I do.
嘿  嗨 你那弄好了
Hey. Hey, you all done in there?
弄完了  她超喜g
Oh, yeah. And... she loves it.
哦 太好了 她喜g那黑色的P室那我就放心了
Oh, great. I'm so glad that she loves her black bedroom.
明天早上我阮和塔去哈丁登
So, I'm gonna register Juan and Lita at Harding in the morning.
你去高中
And then you can take Lizzy to the high school.
你看他的鞋子了]  我明天得他去趟商
Did you see their shoes? We might want to take them to the mall tomorrow.
孩子  吃了
Hey, kids, dinner!
什么  哪阕炖镎f出砗直不可思h
What? That sounds insane coming out of your mouth.
我有孩子了  然了 是三
Do we have kids? Yeah, three of 'em.
太酷了  直不能相信
That's insane! I don't believe it!
你不知道  他就在@里啊
Did you not know that? 'Cause they're really here.
天  天  是真的
Holy shit. Holy shit. Yeah. Yeah.
他就在@里呢  我勰
They're here. I love you.
怎么了  再H一下  再H一下
What? Kiss again! Kiss again!
天
God. Mmm!
@怎么  再H一  再H一
What about that one? Kiss again! Kiss again!
那很L很奇怪的
It's gonna be long and weird.
可以了吧  好了吧
How 'bout that? How 'bout that?
-快c  傻笑的小姑娘  坐  -我去QP子
Come on, giggly. Sit down. I'm gonna shift the plates.
好了  好多好吃的  有h堡 意面 有
Great. We have everything. We have burgers and pasta and... Can
可以吃薯l
we have potato chips?
湎丛璋
Let's get ready for the tub.
你  l想
Uh, you two, come on. Who wants to...
嘿
Hey!
那真的不是洗澡的玩具
That's not really a bath toy.
我不想要@
I don't want this.
e e  那 怎么了 嘿 嘿
Oh, no! That's gonna... What? Hey! Hey!
我下次得弄固定器
I'm gonna get a hamper next time.
嘿  下次
Hey, next time...
你需要  你看
You need...? Lookit!
抓 抓牢 e它沉下去
Grab... Hold it. Keep it over the sink, please.
_水了
Did you flush, sweetie?
晚安  孩子   晚安
Good night, kiddo. Good night.
好
Good night!
我是不是o他晚安吻的   我也不知道
Should we give them a kiss good night? I don't know.
要不你去或者我等  我去下
Maybe you should ask, or should we wait? Should I ask?
我去   你可以直接M砼
I'll ask. You guys are overthinking this.
不好意思  不好意思
Sorry, guys. Sorry.
晚安  晚安
Good night. Good night.
晚安
Good night!
那我是不是也o晚安吻
Should we kiss Lizzy good night?
我就不用了  晚安  哦 晚安 好孩子
I'm good. Good night. Oh. Night, kiddo.
好的 晚安
All right. Good night.
我已很努力m他了
We try so hard to engage with him,
但是不管我怎么做  杰克就只是呆在他的房g里
but no matter what we do, Jake just wants to hang out in his room,
打 fK {咒R人
talking on his phone, swearing, taking the Lord's name in vain,
[弄音 一待一整天
and cranking his explicit music till all hours.
又在W校打架
And he got into another fight at school.
好]有重幼@的其他小朋友
Thank heaven he didn't seriously hurt one of the other kindergartners.
五q的小孩子有手C倒是]什么
I think maybe it's okay for a five-year-old to have a cell phone.
但是他有很多系人
But does he have a lot of contacts?
我D看下的 但是那是他H生o他的
We tried to take it, but his birth mother gave it to him,
我一碰 就 嗯
and if we touch it, it's just... Mmm.
很抱歉  你f的太α
I'm so sorry. You are so right.
他根本不需要手C
He doesn't need a phone.
我再的 然要
We're gonna try again. Definitely try.
好了  彼得和艾莉十天前ё吡巳孩子
Okay, and Pete and Ellie took in three children ten days ago,
有十q的
one of which is a teenager.
是的 一切利
Yeah, it's going pretty good.
我的孩子我意R到我之前的生活有多o聊
I think our kids made us realize just what kind of a rut we were in before.
不是f多o聊  就是一成不 你明白
Not really a rut. Just the same old routine. You know?
上班  健身  吃  喝水  看影
Work, go to the gym, grabbing dinner, drinks, the movies.
你明白我在f什么  不  我不明白
You know what I mean. No, we don't know.
她是在f我之前的生活需要挑
I think she's just trying to say that we needed a new challenge,
需要打破@N握{的生活
maybe something to break up the monotony.
但是孩子打破的不只是握{的生活
That's not the only thing they're gonna break.
我知道起  我知道我每人都要v些痛苦
I know it sounds... I know everyone's going through tough stuff.
但是@些孩子  我X得他非常好 我很幸\
But these kids, I think they're really good. We got lucky.
是他比^幸\ 是的，你中彩票了
They got lucky. Yeah, you hit the jackpot, lady.
大家e@
Guys.
有@么好笑
Why is this funny?
我猜他可能是有c想到度蜜月的r候砝假了
I think they might be recognizing a little bit of a honeymoon period.
不不  是有c像  但是不像是砝假
No, we thought of that. But it doesn't feel like a period.
我是f也并不是完美的
Well, I mean, it's not perfect.
塔只吃薯l
Lita won't eat anything but potato chips.
我正在想k法解Q  我是f我也不是完美的父母
But we got a plan to work on that too. I'm not saying we're perfect
parents.
真的
Are you sure?
我怎么出硪稽c嫉妒啊
And I think I might be recognizing a little bit of jealousy.
各位  @可不是好F象
It's not a good trait, guys.
我在@干嘛呢
Okay, what do we have here?
啊  ^圣Q啊
Huh? Christmas!
@是啥  pxC  你X得怎么
What is it? It's a sewing machine! What do you think?
不好 她不喜g 槭裁窗
No? She doesn't like it? Why not?
看著像C器人啊 老弟  塔  你看@大箱子
Looks like a robot, buddy! Lita, look at this big box!
哥  它f走路  @可能是我的^盔
Dude, it walks and talks. This could be my helmet!
那@些Y物呢   我要是有C器人我高d的
What about the presents? I would've went crazy if I got a robot.
我玩那C器人   @可以宇宙w船
I'm playing with that robot. And this could be the spaceship.
我可以M去  然可以
Can I go inside? Sure.
嘿，孩子，哇，你真的很喜g玩箱  哈
Hey, guys. Wow, you really like cardboard boxes, huh?
有人喜g@花了三小r弄好的玩具屋感d趣
Is anybody interested in playing with the giant dollhouse it took
花了我三小rMb
three hours to assemble?
是b在大盒子里的
Did it come in a big box?
是的  在一值200美元的大盒子里
Yeah, it did. It came in a big $200 box.
我走
Let's go! Let's go!
戆  去拿箱子了
Come on. Let's go get the box.
圣Q就是要玩箱子  ]e
Christmas is boxes. Yes.
嘿    @是o你的
Hey, Lizzy, this one's for you too.
圣Q快  哇哦
Merry Christmas. Oh.
另一  是的
Another one. Yeah.
xx  圣Q  圣Q快
Thanks. Merry... Merry Christmas.
其]必要o我@么多
You didn't have to get all this stuff for us.
我懂  我懂  但我很芬
I know, I know, but we wanted to.
我很d^  是不是太^了
We were excited. Did we go overboard?
]  ]  ]  呃抱歉
No, no, no! Um, I'm sorry.
我很_心
I'm happy. I am. I...
很_心看到塔和阮能收到
It's nice to see Lita and Juan get presents
不完全是陌生人捐的Y物
that weren't donated from total strangers, so...
嘿    如果你想聊一些事
Hey, Lizzy, if you ever want to talk about anything...
我知道F在是圣Q  你v^些事情
I know it's Christmastime and you may have memories and things.
不不不  我
Oh, no, no, no. I'm... I'm...
我很好
I'm good. I...
你知道  我只是早上忘喝咖啡了
You know what? I just haven't had my morning coffee yet.
我F在去喝一杯
So I'm gonna get that.
你要  好
Do you want some coffee? Sure.
感x上天我一起度^第一圣Q
We want to thank the Lord for our first Christmas together.
感恩碛羞@美味的晚  有
And we want to give thanks for this lovely meal and also this, um,
@些超有意思的板盒子
bounty of super fun cardboard boxes.
阿T  阿T
Amen. Amen.
好了  大家_影
Okay. Tuck in, everybody.
我的薯片呢
Where's my potato chips?
今天晚上]有薯片吃  抱歉小家伙
We're not having chips tonight, munchkin. Sorry.
我要吃薯片  塔
I want my chips. Lita!
彼得和我很努力地做了@D
Pete and I worked really hard on this dinner.
有很多好吃的o你吃
There's lots of yummy food for you to eat.
不要  嘿  嘿  嘿
No! Hey, hey, hey.
等等    e@  我
Hey! Lizzy, Lizzy, please! Lizzy, no, okay? I've got this.
你槭裁ξ液  我想湍惆
Why are you yelling at me? I'm just trying to help you.
我]有吼你
I'm not yelling at...
呃我的_有吼  Σ黄  但是
I'm sor... I am. Just then I was. But it's... Look.
塔  不必f的  呃你f了什么
Lita, don't do what Lizzy said. What did you say? C uatro? "Go to
回房g
your bedroom"?
不  @~意思是夸  就像一夸牛奶
No, cuatro means "quart." Like quart of milk.
她f  ]有薯片吃  但你可以喝
She said, "You're not gonna have a potato chip, but you will drink
牛奶
that milk."
之  我可以
In any case, we have this. It's fine.
好吧  行  好
Okay. Fine. Okay.
L一下肉吧  好么
Let's try some of this meat loaf, okay?
不要  我要薯片  ]有薯片o你吃
No! I want my chips! You're not having chips!
我X得她不你的
I don't think she's getting on board with the plan, honey.
我不要@  嘿
I don't want this! Hey!
你_定不o她c薯片  不  不o她的
You sure you don't wanna give her chips? No, we're not giving her chips.
塔  回
Lita, stay right there!
我天  Σ黄  抱歉
Oh, God, I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
]P系  e哭  放松
No, it's okay. Don't cry. Relax.
心_下  抬_
Watch your feet, okay? Raised feet!
我不是故意的  真的Σ黄
I didn't mean to. I'm so sorry.
把薯片o我
You give those to me.
嗷  冷o  e哭
Ow! Ow. Calm down. Don't cry.
我要吃薯片
I want my chips!
e  阮
Just stay there, Juan.
@土豆真的很好吃
These are really, really good potatoes.
我的天  你好  我天  等下
Oh, my God. Are you okay? Oh, God. Hold on.
塔  我去
Lita, duck!
你在做什么  我在想k法缁鸢
What are you doing? Look, I'm trying to put it out!
用番茄u  缁
With ketchup? Put it out!
好了  塔呢
All right. Lita?
等下  什么音
Wait, wh-what's that noise?
她槭裁催@  上的n里]有教@
Why is she growling? That wasn't in the classes. I got nothing for
怎么k
that.
她拿了刀
She's got a knife.
只是海d的刀  那也是刀啊
It's just a SpongeBob knife. It's still a knife.
把刀放下
Just put the knife down, honey.
孩子  放下武器  好
Look, kid, just put down the weapon, okay?
你想我硖理  是你依f可以
You guys want me to deal with this, or do you still got it?
她兔Π  好  好好好吧
Do you wanna let her jump in here now, please? Okay, okay. Fine.
行
Fine!
xx
Gracias.
艾莉  你得W一c西班牙Z
Ellie, you gotta learn some Spanish.
小孩喝的牛奶槭裁从貌ＡПb  Σ黄  我]
Why would you give a kid milk in a glass cup? I'm sorry. I didn't.
她干嘛@  我她
Why did she do that? I hate her!
才]多久  他已我了
That didn't take long. They hate us already.
呃  _切地f  她是f你
Well, technically, she said she hates you.
好好好  我要芭比
Okay, okay, okay! I want a Barbie!
@都不算是真的芭比娃娃
This isn't even a real Barbie.
之前圣Q老人都o了你一真的芭比了
You've got a real Barbie that Santa gave you a few weeks ago.
圣Q老人o我的是胖的芭比  我要一瘦的
Santa got me a fat Barbie! I want a skinny Barbie!
她不胖  那是健康的身材
She's not fat. She's body positive.
如果你把娃娃放下  我o你I超大的圣代吃
If you put the doll back, I'll get you a giant ice cream sundae.
所以你是在钏@行
So you're rewarding this behavior?
你在想什么  你硖理吧
What are you thinking? You handle it.
阮  出戆珊  e打我  e打我  我e了
Juan, get out of there. Please? Don't hit me! Don't hit me! I'm sorry!
我]有打他  好  我]打^他
I didn't hit him, okay? I never have hit him.
我不打孩子的  我想要芭比
I would never hit a kid. I want a Barbie!
停下  不然]有午也]有晚吃
Stop right now, or you're not getting lunch or dinner.
我不是要l挨I  好  我硖理
We're not starving people here, okay? I have this under control.
嘿  你胖婊子
Yeah, Lizzy, you body-positive whore!
你完了 o我  把它o我
Okay, you're done. Gimme that. Give it to me. Just give me that now!
噢  看起硪磺斜M在你掌握呢
Oh, yeah? Yeah, it really looks like you've got it.
哌M去  快c  不  我不要@
Scan it! Hurry! No! We're not doing this!
有人下砹  彼得  你在哪里  彼得人呢
Someone videotaping this? Pete, where are you? Where's Pete?
你完了  行你出去了  真是太感x了
You're done. Oh, great. You're out there? Thank you so much.
我把_砹
Hey, sweetie. I brought the car.
省你走路的rg  T前有路要走
Saved you a little walking time. We had a front space.
好吧  但也很近了
Well, it's still closer.
嘿  彼得  看@新娃娃漂亮吧  哇哦
Hey, Pete, look at my pretty new doll. Wow.
所以你是妥f了  ]有
So you caved, huh? No, I did not cave.
我Io她的  只要四美金
I bought it for her. It was only four bucks.
我能x_@里了  你小鬼
Can we just get out of here, you coward?
P槽  他砹
Holy shit. There they are.
嘿    杰瑞  他到了
Hey, Jan, Jerry. They're here.
噢我天  T蹭到了保r捷
Oh, man! Kid dinged a Porsche.
伙你在做什么  Σ黄  Σ黄
Dude, what are you doing? I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
好吧  e哭  好
All right. Just don't cry, okay?
他需要留l了
He's gonna have to leave a note.
就臀野|西拿出  塔  塔
Just help get the stuff out of the back. Lita! Lita! Honey.
艾莉看起硐衩水了  看起砗茉愀
Ellie looks dehydrated. She looks bad.
我Я诵┡_  阮  你在做什么
We've got the pizza! Juan, whoa, whoa. What are you doing, bud?
噢Σ黄  噢天啊
Oh, sorry! Oh, Christ.
好暖和  嘿  把披_放下
It's so warm. Hey, put the pizza down.
你不能那幽弥  嗨
You can't hold it like that. Hi, Mom.
嘿  爸爸
Hey, Dad.
你一定就是
You must be Lizzy.
恩  嗨  @是塔和阮
Yeah, hi. I'm Lizzy. Um, this is Lita and Juan.
你好  塔
Hello, Lita.
你好  阮
Hello, Juan.
我是外婆  胡恩  @是外公  胡瑞
I'm Grammy "Hw-an" and this is Grandpa "Hw-erry."
可以正常cf
Mom, can you just talk like a normal person?
我喜gJ的l音
I like the way she says her J's.
拜托  很高
Can you please? It's sophisticated.
o你  xx
Here you go, brother. Thanks, man.
我不敢相信  他就和正常孩子一
I can't get over it. They look just like normal kids.
你X得他看起像什么  小海I
What did you think they were gonna look like? Little pirates?
不知道  他太可哿
I don't know. They're just so cute.
新W校怎么
How is the new school?
挺好的  就像  呃  就像W校
It's good. It's like... It's, um... It's school.
哇  很棒
Yeah. Awesome.
那男朋友呢  有]有心
And what's the boy situation? Anything exciting?
ee  e┧了
No, no. Hey, hey, leave her alone.
她不喜g@些
She doesn't like talking about that kind of stuff, so just go easy.
怎么  你不喜g的
What? You don't.
其是有叫雅各布的男生  是
Actually, there's this one guy, Jacob. Yeah?
哇哦  很可鄣拿字  雅各布  我挺喜g的杰克
Wow, that's a cute name. Jacob. I like... Like Jake.
不不  是胡各布
No, honey, it's "Hway-cob."
胡各布
Right? Right? "Hway-cob."
不  不  就是雅各布
No, no, it's just Jacob.
Χ且他不是可鄣母杏X
Yeah, and he's not cute.
是cg庀⒌某墒祛型
He's more of like an artsy, old soul type.
我也矶疾幌g可坌偷
I was never into the cute ones either.
恩  可鄄辉趺春
Nah. Cute's overrated.
是的  我也不喜g  我]有交^性感的男朋友
Right? I didn't either. I've never had a hot boyfriend, ever.
]嘴
Shut up!
?  你看起砭拖裰缓镒  ?
? You look like a monkey ?
?  你起硪蚕袷呛镒  ?
? And you smell like one too ?
桌上可以把手C放下
Lizzy, can we put the phone away while we're at the table, like we
像我之前f的那
talked about?
放下  把她手Co我
Lizzy, please. Give her the phone.
嘿朋友快看  那有好蚩
Hey, guys, check it out. There's some shit going down. Lizzy, the
手C
phone.
o我
Now.
那是她的H生母H  好狠的一招
Is that her real mom? Yeah, that's a harsh move.
H上  如果你看了福斯特的育t
Actually, if you read your foster parent regs,
拿走任何私人物品是不被允S的
you know you're not allowed to take away any of my personal property,
所以
so...
@表情  就是@表情  我要去拿c番茄u
It's the look. She's doing the look. I gotta get some ketchup.
彼得  你f^下次她再@么^分你采取行拥
Pete, you'd said you'd say something to her next time she acts all bitchy.
我]f^婊膺@次  是她f的  不是我
I never said the word "bitchy." It was her word, not mine.
因槟矶疾辉  每一次我都是那娜
I am always the bad guy because you're never there.
我不因橐工作而道歉
I'm not gonna apologize for working.
要有人在你I的房子我破a前
Somebody's gotta deal with that dump of a house you bought before it
搞定它
bankrupts us.
我I的  你也喜g啊  而且那根本不是PI
I bought? You loved it too. And that's not even the point.
PI是你在F  你任他各N逍b法外
The point is, when you are there, you let them get away with murder.
昨晚吃完不肯清理@c
I got on Lizzy just last night when she wouldn't clean up after
我就管教了她
dinner!
完美爸
Perfect parent, huh?
@很好笑  基特  我J槲都X得挺有趣的
Is this funny, Kit? I think we're all enjoying this a little bit,
Σ黄  抱歉  ]P系
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. It's okay.
看白人吵架我目床
I never get tired of watching white people fight.
我也是
Nor do I.
但是槭裁床焕潇o一下
But why don't you calm down
除了互相怪  告V大家  PI的}是什么
and tell us, without blaming each other, what the main issues are.
好吧  塔一直
Well, Lita is just constantly...
我要   我不要
I want... I don't want to!
阮不肯铀的X子
And Juan just doesn't use his head.
解i下窗  而且如果我要f些什么
Unlock the window! And if I say anything about any of it...
我真的很Σ黄  不是我的e
I'm so sorry. It's not my fault.
最壅f的就只是  e管我了
Lizzy's favorite pastime is just... Just leave me alone!
xx我t到
Thanks for making me late.
你是混蛋
You're an asshole.
我著教育小的  不  那可是
God forbid we actually try to parent the little ones. No, no, that's
她的I地
her territory.
e忘了  十qr  她的r不r就消失
Don't forget, when Lizzy was ten her mother would disappear for weeks
Y拜
at a time,
留下自照阮和塔
leaving Lizzy to parent Juan and Lita all by herself.
她不袖手旁^你z全嘭
Yeah, she's not just gonna step aside and let you two take over.
你是f我她碚疹小的  你有
Are you saying that we should let her parent the kids? Are you
在
paying attention?
她只有15q  是糟糕的家L  她需要成楹⒆
She's 15. She's a terrible parent. She needs to be a kid.
F在你要站出砼力成楦改
Now, you gotta step up and become the parents.
但你f她不我  是的她不
But you just said she won't let us. Nope, she won't.
你知道么  P  大多登r下你都很好
You know, Karen, you've been a godsend through most of this,
但我F在快被你惹懒
but you're just about to piss me off!
情r不改直到你_成共R
You won't get anywhere with her until you two get on the same page.
是  ]e
Right? That's right.
下次她再表F得不友善  一下三R法t
If she's hostile with you again, maybe try using the three R's.
第一l  控制情w
Okay? Number one: regulate.
不如档绞  深呼吸
"Lizzy, why don't you take some deep breaths, count to ten."
第二l  拉近距x
Number two: relate.
我明白你很y受  ]有l愿意v@些
"I understand that you're upset. Nobody likes to feel this way."
很不e  第三l  f明理由
That's good. Number three: reason.
生馐钦常的
"Lizzy, it's okay to be angry.
但是威{要在深夜我睡著r
What's not okay is to threaten to slash our throats
o我脖子硪坏毒筒辉趺春昧
in the middle of the night when we're asleep."
抱歉  我是不是
I'm sorry, did I...?
@是H上  我的故事
That was actually us.Our story.
]e  上一次提到的
Yeah. Last session.
但小家伙]有猿忠@么做
The little guy didn't follow through with it though.
r]有  -r]
Well, not yet! Not yet.
抱歉  我不笑
Sorry, but we shouldn't be laughing.
不  H上碛羞@拥挠哪感也是重要的
No, it's actually important to have a sense of humor about this kind of thing
]e  多笑笑  不然o法挺^去
Right. You gotta laugh or you'll never make it through this.
是的
That is right.
f到@  下一位到W克托布
Speaking of which, next up we have October,
]有和孩子配Τ晒
who still hasn't been matched with a child.
K于是有些好消息
Well, there's some good news.
我一起Q定哪部分家
So, together we're all gonna decide which chore we'd like to do
每周再Q
and then each week we'll mix it up.
我可以  喂米堡  可以啊
Can I do "Feed Meatball"? Yes!
我想喂米堡  你可以下周喂他
I want to feed Meatball! You can feed him next week.
彼得  我希望她不是J真弄@些
Pete, I hope she's not serious about all this.
不只是她  是我  并且我是f真的
It's not just she, it's we. And we are. Very serious.
好吧  所以你是想我湍洗_  不
Okay, so do you want us to wash your feet too? Oh, Lizzy.
都是狗屁    嘿  等一下
This is bullshit! Lizzy! Hey, hey, wait, wait!
我  些e的
Lizzy. Let's just... Let's... Let's try something else.
我休息下  冷o下  深呼吸
Can we just take a moment, calm down, and take a few breaths?
好
Please?
看
Try it.
很好  很好  我明白你@些感到很oZ
Nice! Nice. And we hear you that you're frustrated with the chart.
]e  我X得很oZ
Well, yeah. Yeah, I'm frustrated.
是的  oZ很正常  我也都有c沮
Yes! And that's okay to be frustrated! We're all frustrated.
我想想下一次怎么更好表_自己
So let's think about next time how we can express ourselves better.
好好  好吧
Okay. Okay. Well...
我不清楚  或S下次你
I don't know, maybe next time you guys...
ξL一下三R法t
try and use the three R's on me.
我可以吐一地  因樘盒牧
I could barf all over the ground because it's so nauseating!
我就知道@λ]用
I knew it wasn't gonna work with her.
哇太棒了  你在家
Oh, good! You're home!
嗨
Hi!
f了要ll短信或者打啊
Mom, I told you to text or call.
你告V我o你字馨差D一下
You told me to give you a few weeks to settle in.
F在已^了字芰  而且我想看看我的O子O女
Well, it's been a few weeks, and I want to meet my new grandkids.
你肯定是吧  ^
You must be Lizzy. Come here!
不  她不喜g  磉@
No, she doesn't like it when you... Come here!
喔  我是你的奶奶珊迪
Oh! I'm your Grandma Sandy.
任何人想欺你  他都要先^我@P
Anyone ever starts shit with any of you, they have to deal with me.
我F在是一家人了  我永h是你的后盾  你到了
We're family now, and I got your back forever. You hear me?
eo  拜托  哦  我的天
Mom, just take it easy. Please. Oh, my God!
我能看看他
Will you look at them!
阮  塔  @是珊迪  @是彼得的
Juan, Lita, this is Sandy. This is Pete's mom.
嗨  嗨
Hi! Hi!
真想把你吃了  我的大O子怎么影
I could just eat you two up! And how's my baby boy?
噢
Ohh!
你好  H鄣  嗨
Hello, dear. Hi.
o我追昼  我正在_家庭h呢
Mom, give us a few minutes. We were just in the middle of a family meeting.
太好了  我也是@家庭的一T了
Perfect, because I'm a member of the family.
珊迪奶奶有一件事要宣布
Grandma Sandy has an announcement to make.
我o全家人都I了去六面旗主}公@的票
I got the whole family tickets to Six Flags!
耶  耶
Yay! Yay!
六面旗是什么
What's Six Flags?
六面旗是什么    @提h很好
"What's Six Flags?" Mom, that's such a nice offer.
但@里的情r有c碗s  我得把一切都理好
But things have been a little chaotic around here, and we need things to be normal.
我砀嬖V你什么]有理好  你的孩子不知道什么是六面旗
I'll tell you what's not normal, is your kids not knowing what Six Flags is.
你的孩子
Your kids.
F在不是r候  我]有在f@件事  好
Ma, it's just not a good time. So we're not doing this, okay?
我]有在f@件事    我在管理上_成共R了
We're not doing this, right? We're on the same page because of the structure thing?
好吧  好吧
Yeah, yeah.
H鄣  是  艾莉
Honey? Right, El?
我才]屈服  哦  你屈服了
I did not cave. Oh, you caved.
看了你一眼  你就屈服了
Lizzy gave you the look and you caved.
也S我只想做孩子_心的父母而不是喝
Maybe I just wanted to be the fun parent for once instead of being the bad guy.
我在著做娜  你不我做  好吧  是的  我很抱歉
I tried being the bad guy. You wouldn't let me. Okay, fine. I'm sorry.
但每人看起矶己荛_心啊
But look how much fun everybody's having.
她真的在笑  @太狂了
And Lizzy, she's actually smiling. It's crazy.
嘿  你玩得_心
Hey! Did you have fun?
你不必去玩和玩的那些目
You don't have to go on the kiddie rides.
我喜g刺激的  你想去
I love the big rides. You want to go on the...
嘿    嘿  怎么了
Hey, Lizzy! Hey, what's up?
很高d到你  很高d到你
Good to see you! Good to see you too!
嘿  嘿  怎么了
Hey, hey. What's up?
呃  P莉  莎凡娜  他是我的  嗯
Uh, Kylie, Savanna, these are my, um...
B父母
fosters.
是的  是的  我是她的B父母
Yeah, yeah. We're the fosters!
待  H上  我正要去水上@呢
I'll see you guys later. Actually, we were just gonna go on the water ride.
她和朋友一起去吧
Let her go with her friends.
她可不想和你老家伙混呆在一起
They don't want to be stuck here with a bunch of old farts like you two.
她想Tc刺激的|西  看看哥什么的
They want to ride the big stuff and check out the hot boys.
@是一百元
Here's a hundred.
o自己I些o念品和好吃的
Buy yourselves some souvenirs and junk food.
嗯嗯  xx  珊迪奶奶  xx
Uh-huh. Thanks, Grandma Sandy. Thanks!
好吧  酷
All right, cool.
呃  什么r候回你家
Uh, meet you guys at... What time are we going back to your house?
我回自己的家  我都住在那里  七c
We're going back to our house, where we all live, at 7:00!
好的  到r候  再
Okay, I'll see you then. Bye!
你在干什么  你不能  哦  不
Mom, what are you doing? You can't... Oh, no!
小阮被垃圾桶卡住了
Little Juanny's upchucking in the trash bin!
你]事吧
You all right, peanut?
把才吃的漏斗蛋糕都吐了
Was it all the funnel cakes we ate?
哦  哦  哦
Oh. Oh, oh.
我知道她收到了@些短信  我能看到@些c
I know she's getting these texts. I can see the dots.
也S她跑掉了  也S她出了什么事
Maybe she ran off. Maybe something happened to her.
不  她]有  她只是把我又作一B父母了
No, she didn't. She's just treating us like another set of fosters.
好啦  再
All right, bye.
xx你送我回  我勰
Thanks for the ride. I love you!
我要娜肆  注意c  再
I'm the bad guy. Watch this. Bye.
再  嘿
Bye! Hey!
你到底去在哪毫  我去看影了
Where the hell were you? We went to the movies.
rgL了c  ]什么大不了的
And it ran a little bit later. It's not a big deal.
你就不能花五秒碜我知道你]有被人\
You couldn't have taken five seconds to let us know nobody murdered you?
好吧  你猜怎么著   你被禁足了
Well, guess what? You're grounded.
我被禁足了  是的  你被禁足了  因槲把你禁足了
I'm grounded? Yeah. You're grounded. Because I just grounded you.
在你]有被禁足之前  你]事
Before you weren't grounded, you weren't anything,
然后我f了我才f的  F在你被禁足了
and then I just said that thing that I said, and now you're grounded!
我已等了你一小r了  我懋娜  冷o
We've been waiting one hour for you! I'm the bad guy. Calm down.
他懋娜  你哪阂膊荒苋チ
He's the bad guy. You're not going anywhere.
你完了  完了
You're done! Done!
不想  你知道
Don't want to hear it! You know what?
我九q的r候住在一破房子里
When I was nine I lived in a crack house.
所以我非常肯定影院是安全的h境
So I'm pretty sure the multiplex is a comparatively safe environment.
哦  不  不  就因槟阌羞^麻┎淮表@次就]事了
Oh, no. No. You don't play that trouble pass card with us.
你完蛋了  小姑娘
Your butt's in a sling, missy!
哦  珊迪奶奶  我忘了  什么
Oh, Grandma Sandy, I forgot. What?
我o你Я  嗯
I got you, um...
哦  天
Oh, sweet Jesus.
看看@  我每天都要穿著它
Will you look at this? I'm gonna wear it every day.
哦  ^
Oh, come here.
你知道  @提醒了我
You know, this reminds me
彼得和他那些狐朋狗友偷^一v披_卡
of when Pete and his degenerate friends stole a pizza truck.
她很好  她很好  哦  天哪
She's good. She's good. Oh, God.
你z要整晚都站在那
Are you two gonna stand there all night,
是我要孩子按r睡X呢
or are we gonna try to get these kids to bed at a decent hour?
你得我告V^你我做的hh不
You remember I told you we weren't special enough for this?
我做得很好  你f我是墨守成的
We were doing fine. You said that we were in a rut.
也S我被牧  不喜g一成不的生活
Maybe we were spoiled and didn't appreciate the rut.
那N生活味安o  你知道  我有c涯盍  但你非要
The rut was easy and quiet. You know, I miss the rut. But you had to be a mommy.
去和青少年是l的主意
Whose idea was it to go and talk to the teenagers?
我不能找不l表意不穿丁字的小孩吧
We could've had a toddler who doesn't have opinions and thong underwear.
什么  你把我推M了下一哟蔚子里
What? You pushed us into some next-level shit!
著  我不能在@里互相挑
Look, we can't start turning on each other here.
如果我保持冷o一起鸲
If we just stay calm and we work together,
我可以找到k法把@些小混蛋s出我的房子
we can find a way to get these little assholes out of our house!
F在我正在f啊
Now we're talking!
我就是@么想的  你好
That's exactly what I was thinking. Hello!
我非常他  我也是  他最牧
I hate them so much. Me too. They're the worst.
他太忘恩x了  我樗做了一切
They're so ungrateful. We're doing everything for them.
他s他什么都不能o我  是吧
And they could give two shits. Right?
但你猜怎么著  他]有被正式收B
But guess what? They're not adopted yet.
不  不  他]有
No. No, they're not.
我可以
We could just...
把他就送回去
put 'em back.
我是f  是的  我看起硐袷澜缟献畈畹娜  但是
I mean, yes, we would look like the worst people in the world, but...
是的  我的  F在每人都J槲是圣人
Yeah, we would. And right now everybody thinks we're saints.
我知道  我喜g@一c  我真的很喜g@一c  @是唯一的c了
I know. I love that part. I do love that part. That's the only good part.
我有主意
Just an idea.
如果我f有H戚砹四
What if we say that some relatives came forward?
法庭把他ё吡  我o能榱
The courts took 'em. There's nothing we could do.
Π  我再D椎窝I  表F得非常y^
Right? We squirt a few tears, we act super devastated.
那很好  那很好  那非常好
That's good. That's good. That's very good.
然后我就有了干舻姆孔雍图s之夜
And we get our clean house and date night back.
每人都槲感到y^
And everybody feels sorry for us.
是啊  Π
Yes! Right?
也S收些Y物
Get some presents maybe.
我永h不@么做的
We're never gonna do that.
不
No.
@是好主意  但我
It's a nice thought, but we're...
我被困住了  不是  是的  我被困住了
We're stuck, aren't we? Yeah, we are.
你知道  我必承J我犯了一乐氐腻e`
You know, we gotta just accept that we made a terrible mistake
我的生活F在大部分都很糟糕
and our life is mostly gonna suck now.
晚安  H鄣
Good night, honey.
好了  板l蛇各有一子
All right, one nail on each side of the slat.
好的  在啥硕加  可以
Okay. On both ends. Okay?
看  是的  很好
"Look." Yes, excellent.
好的  ^m  把@些拼出
Okay, keep going. Get the words for me.
你在做什么  你想M  你想和打招呼
What are you doing? You want to get in? You wanna say hi to Lizzy?
f曹操曹操到
Speak of the devil.
他在@里干什么
What are they doing here?
你]f^我不能任何人硗
You never said I couldn't have any people over.
每人都知道被禁足的r候是不能有人^淼
Everybody knows you can't have people over when you're grounded.
你也知道  因樗@然是拇暨M淼
You know that too, because they obviously came in through the window.
便f一下  @地方太盒牧
This place is disgusting, by the way.
天  真是{粹婊子  你才f我什么
God, what a Nazi bitch. What did you call me?
我不知道  你就像{粹婊子
I don't know. You just seem like a Nazi bitch.
出去  F在
Get out. Now.
出去  你  出去  去吧  F在  不  你L出我的房g
Out. Both of you, out. Go! Now! No, you get out of my room.
不  不  我要你在@黑屋子里待著  @些人要走了
No, no, I'm staying in your black room. These guys are leaving.
不  拇舫鋈  造反者  哪里淼哪睦锶
No, out the window, Pussy Riot! Way you came in!
出去  F在  P槽
Out, now! Holy shit!
出去  出去
Out! Out!
哦  你真是了
Oh! You're literally crazy!
是你把我逼的  哦  我的天  你在做什么
You're driving me crazy! Oh, my God. What are you doing?
你看起硐精神病患者  l悠
You're acting like you're a psychopath. Start the car.
里面l生了什么    拜托  我f你被禁足了
What is going on in there? Lizzy, please, I said you're grounded.
你要去哪里  我要打o我的社工
Where are you going? I'm calling my caseworker.
好主意  嗯
That's a good idea, huh?
警察  你的弟弟和妹妹打包他的小熊
Get CPS to come, make your little brother and sister pack up their court bears
和垃圾袋然后搬回莫斯科
and trash bags in the middle of the night and move them back to the Muskies?
那λ真好  那也比你好
That'll be really good for them. Better than you.
不  不比我好  我受不了你了  你能理一下  彼得
No! Not better than me! I can't with you. Can you please deal with her, Pete?
嘿    你要  我真是好人
Hey, Lizzy, you're gonna... We're really good people!
我只想o你一完美的家  @硬
We just want to make a nice home for you. Is that so wrong?
你只是一想做慈善收B孤旱陌兹伺士
You're just another white lady who wants to adopt little charity orphans
@能你ψ约焊杏X良好
to make you feel good about yourself.
彼得  你告V她我是什么人  告V她
Pete, you tell her what my nationality is! Tell her!
嗯  事上  她是
Well, actually by blood she is...
我有八分之一的科曼奇族血y  好  所以我不是白人
I'm one-eighth Comanche, okay? So I'm not that white!
我F在看起碛凶晕腋杏X很好
And do I look like I feel good about myself right now?
好吧  那告V我  告V我
Okay, then tell me! Please tell me!
你槭裁赐蝗挥辛讼胍收B孩子的_
Why did you suddenly feel the urge to get foster kids?
因槲  是  我是f  我
Because we... It was... I mean, I...
彼得  求你了  就是@  不  我
"Pete, please?" Exactly. No, I...
嘿  你哪憾疾荒苋  站住
Hey, you're not going anywhere. Stop right there!
我是J真的  e打_那扇T
I mean it. Don't open that door.
嘿  e上那v  你了
Hey! Do not get in that car. You hear me?
eP那扇T  我是J真的
Don't shut that door. I mean it!
很好  F在我能M去@
Good. Now can we just go inside so we can talk about this?
阮  R上放下
Juan, drop it right now!
你在做什么  把它拿出
What are you doing? Take it out!
-不  最好在到t院之前e铀  你]事的  伙  我在呢
No, better to leave it in till we get to the hospital. You're okay, buddy. We're here.
我在@里  你]事的
We're here. You're okay.
猿忠幌  我得把它包起
Stay still. I got to wrap it up.
放p松  我R上送你去t院  好  你是
Relax. We'll get you there in one second, okay? You're...
哦  H鄣  阮]事的  戆
Oh, honey, Juan is gonna be okay. Come on.
你知道  告V女孩我需要他的  F在
You know what? Tell the girls we need their car. Now!
出  快c  悠  快c
Get out! Move your ass! Come on!
我在呢  孩子  我在呢  -上  上  上
I got you, buddy. I got you. Get in, get in, get in.
大家系好安全  系好安全
Seat belts on, everybody! Seat belts on.
你是勇敢的孩子  到了  看著我  你真勇敢  Π
You're a brave boy, you hear me? Look at me. You're so brave. Yeah?
你做的太棒了  伙  我就在@里呢
You're doing such a good job, buddy. We're right here.
你好  嘿  救救他
Hello! Hey, help, please.
l生什么事了  他_上有根子
What happened? He's got a nail in his foot.
我不想拿出硪苑廊f一
I didn't want to take it out, just in case.
那很明  把他放在@床上
That was very smart. Put him right on this gurney.
嘿  伙  ]事的  伙  我在@呢
Hey, buddy. It's all right, buddy. We're here.
你是母H  是的  哦  我是他的B母
Are you the mother? Yes. Oh, I'm his foster mom.
好的  @走  爸爸
Okay. Right this way, Dad.
嘿  伙  你叫什么名字
Hey, buddy, what's your name?
阮  我要把@清理干  o你打一麻醉
Juan, we're gonna clean this off, give you a little anesthetic,
然后把子拿出
and then take this nail out.
握住我的手  可能有c疼  看著我
Hold my hand. Gonna be a little pinch. Look at me.
抓住我的手  抓住我的手  有c刺痛
Hold my hand, hold my hand. A little bit of a sting.
停下  住手  快好了
Stop! Stop! It's almost over.
就是@  好了  好了  好了
That's it. It's done! It's done. It's done.
我想我塔去大d
I think we should take Lita to the lobby.
你想和她一起去是留下砼闳钅
You want to go with her or stay here with Juan?
你抱著她吧
You take her.
^  嘿  我就在@
Come here. Hey, I'm right here.
]事了  你真勇敢
He's okay. You're so brave.
你做得太好了  伙
You're doing so good, buddy.
所以他不必穿石膏什么的  只是p
So he doesn't have to wear a cast or anything? It's just stitches?
是的  好吧  @是好消息
Yeah. Well, that's good news.
@是怎么l生的呢
And how did this happen?
@是我的e  我走_了  把留在了那里
It was my fault. I walked away, and I left the gun there.
阮把它炝似  不  不是他的e  是我的e
Juan just picked it up. No. It wasn't their fault. It was mine.
我想_x_  但我不x_
I was trying to leave in a car and I wasn't supposed to,
然后他分心了  然后我θ畲蠛按蠼
and then they got distracted, and then I yelled at Juan,
然后他手上的掉到了_上
and he dropped the thing on his foot...
e扯淡了  我不把留在那
Don't be ridiculous. I should never have left the nail gun there.
彼得  ]嘴  @就是他孩子搬走的原因  好
Pete, shut up! This is the kind of stuff they move kids for, okay?
@不是他的e  他什么都]做
It wasn't their fault. They didn't do anything.
我是犯了e的人  ]P系
I should be the one getting in trouble right now. It's okay.
你槭裁床贿^磉@里呢  抱歉
Why don't you come on over here? Excuse me.
我碚l生了什么
And, uh, let's talk about what happened.
所以  呃  ]有人被搬走
So, uh, nobody's being moved.
嘿  怎么了
Hey. What's wrong?
呃  我不知道  今天早上我醒
Uh, I have no idea. I just woke up this morning and...
死的
Damn it.
你知道  我想我能兔
You know what? I think I can help.
我有一
I have a...
我有一很棒的梳子  要不要我
I have this really great detangler. You want me to...?
然  是的  是的  管他呢  然了  是
Sure, yeah. Yeah, whatever, yeah. Yeah?
好吧  @里
Okay, here.
坐下  我  是啊
Have a seat, and I'll... Yeah.
好的
Okay.
哇  怎么@  我不知道
Wow. How'd this happen? I don't know.
是啊  如果拽到^l了就跟我f  好
Yeah. Just let me know if it pulls, okay?
好的  搞定了
Okay. That's good.
好多了  是吧  哦  哇  是啊  xx了
Better, yeah? Oh, wow. Yeah. Thank you.
我再把它弄c
Let me just smooth it out for you.
xx了
Thank you.
]P系  一切都^去了
No problem. It's all gone.
都浜昧  浜昧
You all set? Yep.
嘿  xx你的午餐  ]P系
Hey, thanks for the lunch. No problem.
哦  那是雅各布
Oh, is that that boy Jacob?
炝死圾的那
The one that just picked up that bit of trash?
e大@小怪  ]有  我槭裁匆大@小怪呢
Don't freak out about it. No! Why would I freak out about it?
就像你f的  他看起硐褚g型的人
He looks like an artistic type, like you said.
你真的@么J  然了
You think so? Definitely!
看看那  是啊
Look at that face. Yeah.
挺有任心的  知道把垃圾炱
Conscientious. Picking up trash.
是啊  是  他是
Yeah. Yeah, he is. Yeah.
好的  祝你有愉快的一天  xx  你也是
Well, have a good day. Thanks. You too.
好的  好的
Okay. All right.
小心你的_  阮  再  塔
Careful with your foot, Juan. Bye, Lita.
你看到了
Well, did you see that?
肯定_始不那么恨我了  Π
Definitely starting to hate me a bit less, right?
也S吧
Maybe.
嗨    嘿  查利
Hi, Lizzy. Hey, Charlie.
嗨  雅各布
Hi, Jacob.
怎么了 小  ]什么
Wassup, baby girl? Nothing.
你怎么  我挺好  收拾你的子
How you doing? I'm good. Cleaning up your mess.
你槭裁床辉诮o我惹麻┲前早cMW校呢
Why don't you get into school before you get me in trouble.
好的  ]}
All right, fine.
系我  -]}
Text me. Okay.
嗨  H鄣  嗨
Hey, hon. Hey.
她做得怎么  她挺好的
Hi. How's she doing? She's good.
噢α  有事
Oh. Yeah. And check this out.
我今天到早了  看到我  然后就
I got here early, Lizzy saw me, and she came over and just starts
_始f了
talking.
跟你f  Π
To you? Yeah!
不是那N乖女孩的聊天  也不是平常的冷
Not, like, full-on girl talk, but not the usual silent treatment either.
她居然跟我v了那叫雅各布的男孩
She was telling me about that kid Jacob,
有他不怎么f  她不知道他是不是喜g她
and how he doesn't say much so she can't tell if he likes her.
下一刻我就M入了模式  o她建h  比如
Next thing I know I'm in full mom mode, giving her advice, like,
害羞的男孩有r候你要~出第一步
"Well, sometimes with the quiet types you'll have to make the first move."
你f什么第一步  你她δ泻⑦~出第一步
You said "make a move"? You told her to make a move on a boy?
@是好男孩    相信我
This kid is harmless, baby. Trust me.
]想到她居然喜g他  我想她凵弦哪泻
I'm thrilled she even likes him. I totally pegged her for the bad boys.
怎么回事啦  阮弄牧耸l
What happened? Juan broke Potato Chips.
e哭e哭  我可以修好她的  看  修好啦
Calm down. I'm gonna fix her, okay? Here you go. See?
xx  耙耙
Thanks, Daddy.
你有到  她叫我爸爸
Did you hear that? I just got my first "Daddy"!
你作弊了吧
That's... You suck!
不公平  我也要  嗨  H鄣
No fair! I want some of that. Hey, honey.
塔  我有什么可以偷侥  ]有
Lita, can I help you with anything? Nope!
什么]有  你是跟我f  我是l啊
No, what? Are you talking to me? Who am I?
艾莉  阮    磉@
Ellie. Juan. Buddy, come here!
磉@  乖鹤
Come here, Son.
你的|西好吃  我叫你鹤幽憧梢越邮馨
How's your foot? You okay? You okay if I call you "Son"?
然啦
Sure.
去哪毫  就在那  看得到
Where's Lizzy? Right there. See her?
噢然  她就在那
Oh, yeah, she's right there.
她磉@  然后翻了底朝天
She just comes out here, she takes all this stuff out,
她甚至不用一秒
and she can't bother with the one second it takes
P上@T或者放K|西到水槽里
to close a stupid door or put anything in the sink.
l生了什么  我早上在R桶里找到我的梳子
What happened? I found my hairbrush in the toilet this morning.
什么鬼  我都f了不是我放的
What? I told you that wasn't me!
不是你是l  是我留在浴室o你用的
Of course it was you. I left it in the bathroom for you.
阮和塔都]起床  我起床啦  吵[小姐
Juan and Lita aren't even up yet. I'm up now, Miss Noisy Pants.
Σ黄鸢∥业男  我以槲P系在好
I'm sorry, sweetie. I thought we were really connecting.
我留在那o她用N了坌男”阗N
I left it there for her with a nice little note, with hearts on it and stuff.
我滴天哪  不是我扔MR桶的
Oh, my God. I didn't do it.
哇哦  你好  @是什么鬼
Wow. Hello. What is that?
你穿著@衣服是去衣舞俱凡
You're wearing that? Are you going to a strip club?
Σ黄  我不像你穿得像焦]的沙雕那
Sorry I don't dress like an uptight douche like you.
你不能@雍臀依掀耪f  @是安泰勒w堑囊路O
You don't talk to my wife like that! This is from Ann Taylor. Loft!
安泰勒w  美第一行政品牌
so去穿外套  越多越好
You know what? Go put some clothes on, a lot of them.
然后上  今天早上我送你  我滴天哪
Then get in my truck. I'm driving you this morning. Oh, my God!
你真的很吵O
You guys are so annoying!
去Q衣服  @又不是什么大事
Change the clothes. It's not that big of a deal.
嗨  我穿得像沙雕
Hey. Do I dress like a douche?
]有  看著她她上我的  再啦  耙耙
No. Make sure she gets out to my truck. Bye, Daddy.
再  小
Bye, sweetie.
死我了
Oh, my goodness. Oh.
怎么回事喊
Hey, what's that? Oh!
你]事吧
You okay?
真的太羞u了
That's a shame.
我在干嘛呢  走啦
What are we doing here? Let's go.
我t到的  你知道
I'm gonna be late for school, you know.
M戆
Come on.
哦嚯  所以你F在是wP我咯
Okay. So you're punishing me with manual labor.
我任何r候都比你更努力地活著
I've worked harder than you've ever...
嗯我知道  你很了不起
Yeah, I know, you're a badass.
@不是土P  好吧  嗨
This isn't a punishment, okay? Hey!
我是Stewart  你就是  你好
I'm Stewart. You probably... You... What's up?
斯D特e再跟她f好
Stewart. Don't ever talk to her again, okay?
有  你去吃午餐  @才八c十五分O
As a matter of fact, go to lunch. It's 8:15.
好吧  午餐rg
Okay. Lunch it is.
^
Come on.
把@些穿上  什么鬼
Put these on. What?
eU  穿上
Just put them on.
我知道你很生
Lizzy, I know you're angry.
不爽我  不爽@世界  可能也有c不爽你自己
At us, at the world. Maybe at yourself a little bit.
我不知道  你又不肯f
I don't know, and you're not talking.
事是  我生獾r候也不想f
Truth is, when I'm pissed, I don't like to talk about it either.
但你知道我生做什么
But you know what I do like to do?
啊  我生r喜g搞破
Oh! I like to break shit.
真的
R... Really?
@屋子里的任何|西
Anything in this room.
砸起  嗯嗯
Swing away. Okay.
怎么  感X爽  爽啊
Huh? How'd that feel? It felt good!
]_你吧  嗯嗯
Feels good, huh? I told you. Yeah.
停停停  e浪M  F在我想你臀忙
Now... Whoa, whoa! Don't waste it, all right? I want you to do me a favor.
我需要你想些真的能搞毛你的事
I need you to think about something that really pisses you off.
明白]  明白了
You got it? I got it.
好的呢  砸它
Let's see it. Bust that shit up.
爽
Yes!
爽吧 你喜g不  然  非常爽
There you go. You like that? Yeah, that was good.
好  接著
All right, come on.
爽吧
There we go. Yes!
哈哈p
Ho-ho! Double shot!
爽完了吧
You like that?
超爽的
That was cool.
所以今天不上W了
So no school today, huh?
皮特我去你正在b修的屋子了  嗯哼
Pete took me to the house you're flipping. Hmm.
我做了些了不得的工作  嗯  挺好的
We did some demo work. That's cool.
嗨嗨嗨  ^
Um, hey, hey, come on.
那R桶里的梳子
About that hairbrush?
我H以前是臀沂犷^的
my mom used to brush my hair...
我不知道  很Σ黄
and I don't know, I'm sorry.
]P系的  我也有e
It's okay. I'm sorry too.
不不  你]有e  才不是呢  真的Σ黄
No, you have no reason to be sorry. No, I'm really sorry.
好
All right.
我F在去收拾干  如果你需要的梳子在R桶里
I'm gonna go clean up. Hairbrush is in the toilet, if you need it.
干得漂亮
Good one.
xx
Thank you.
你要@愚D痈觳膊判
You wanna rotate like this, okay?
就是@
Yeah.
阮打我了
Juan hit me!
啊 我的天哪
Oh, no. Oh, God!
嘿  三球T  把你叫^
Hey, number three, where's your mother?
我]事  ]事就好
I'm okay. Okay.
我]有打她
I didn't hit her!
阮你把我手C藏哪毫
Juan, where did you put my phone?
我]有拿你的手C  我真的]有
I didn't take your phone! No, I didn't!
好  第一次L
All right! First try!
-Tres  -Tres
Tres. Tres.
W了]  爸 爸 爸
There you go. Dad, Dad, Dad!
拿好了阮
There you go, Juan.
吐出  吐出
Spit it out, spit it out!
接住  水  不  我需要冰
Here, water! No, we need ice!
水砹 水砹  天哪
Water, water. Here. Oh, gosh.
嘿
Hey.
嘿  小
Hey, buddy.
嘿  嘿  嘿
Hey, hey, hey.
嘿  一切安好呢小  你l噩袅
Hey. It's okay, sweetie. Did you have a bad dream?
嗯嗯  真的啊
Yeah. Yeah?
]有事的  你在被C里很安全
You're okay. You're safe and sound in your bed.
你四肢健在呢
You're good.
晚安啦  小
Good night, buddy.
晚安  嘛嘛
Good night, Mommy.
什么
What?
你f什么了
What did you say?
阮  能在f一次
Juan, what did you say?
你是不是叫我了  阮
Did you say something, Juan?
嘿  阮  你是叫我了吧
Hey, Juan, what did you say?
阮
Juan!
阮  再叫我一次吧  阮
Juan! Did you say something? Juan!
阮  就再f一次嘛
Juan, what did you say?
阮
Juan!
我的天哪
Oh, my God.
晚安啦  小
Good night, buddy.
嘿  嘿
Hey. Hey!
哇哦  @看起砗芡昝勒O   嗯哼  你喜g
Wow, it's looking good. Huh? You like it?
看看那  我按照你意思把Σ毓癜丛诹N房u的M^
Check it out. I put the storage at the end of the island, like you suggested.
哇  @真的太棒了
Oh, hey, yeah, yeah, yeah.
便一提  那真是好主意  太炫酷了吧
Great idea, by the way. It's awesome.
^臀N一些瓦吧  Π
Why don't you come help us hang some tile? Yeah.
不了  我
No, I, uh...
那么  @里有
So, there's, um...
有些事情我想去做
There's something I'd like to do,
我想您臀湟幌
and I was hoping I could get your help setting it up.
]}  我要湫┦裁  什么都行
Sure. What are we setting up? Of course. Anything.
我跟P和莎^
So I was talking to Karen and Sharon, and they...
我月前走了
Uh, my mom got out a few months ago, so...
我最近都]^她  我想和她面
And I haven't seen her. I was hoping I could see her.
可以  ]}  然可以
Yeah, sure. Yeah, of course.
肯定可以的啊  嗯嗯
Of course. I mean, that's... Yeah.
好的  xx您
Cool. Thanks.
]什么  嗯  }不大
Yeah. It's cool. Great.
太xx了
Okay. Thanks.
您  ~
You, uh...
那我就在外面等吧
I'll just wait outside. Okay.
Mom!
嗨
Hi.
Hi, Mom.
阮  塔
Juan, Lita.
嘿  阮  塔  快^
Hey, Juan, Lita, come on!
快砜
Come on.
怎么回事了呢  我想和嘛嘛呆著
What's wrong? Come on. I want to stay with Mom.
你的在那里啊
Your mommy's over there.
]P系的  小  嗯嗯  ]P系的  H鄣
It's okay, sweetheart. It's okay, honey.
我和你一起^去  我就在@里
We're gonna go with you. We're right here.
我一起走吧  快砜
We'll walk together. Come on.
慢c郝
Slow down.
噢  我的孩子  你已@么大了啊
Oh, my babies, you got so big!
斫o我抱抱
Come, mi amor.
嗨  我是休  我是卡拉的社工
Hi, I'm Sue. I'm Carla's caseworker.
你肯定就是皮特和艾莉了  嗯嗯  我是Pete  嗨
You must be Pete and Ellie? Yeah, I'm Pete. Hi.
嗨  我是艾莉
Hey. I'm Ellie.
@是卡拉  她是  孩子的H
This is Carla. She's... Their mom.
嗨  我是艾莉  非常高d到你
Hi. I'm Ellie. Nice to meet you.
我是皮特
I'm Pete.
嘿  我想fxx你兔φ疹他在
Hey, I wanted to say thank you for watching them while I was...
]P系  他都很乖
No problem. They've been doing great.
阮_始W琴了Π  小家伙
Juan started playing piano. Right, buddy?
塔在拼y拿了一百分
And Lita just got 100 on her last spelling test.
的足球打遍天下o呈
And Lizzy's soccer team is undefeated.
好的  那么你四c斫踊匚吧
All right, so you guys gonna pick us up at 4:00?
]}  待
Okay. We'll see you in a bit.
嗯嗯  我很快就回  很快就回
Yeah, we'll be back. We'll be back soon.
再啦  小家伙  很高d到你
Bye, guys. Nice to meet you.
你行
You okay?
xx你照他  我就像做了五月保姆
"Thanks for watching them"? Like we've just been fricking babysitting for five months?
她根本不像我以榈哪
She's just not what I pictured at all.
她  她看起砗苷常
She's... She kind of looks normal.
我感X不太好  就像我在破e人的家庭
I feel bad, like we're breaking up a family.
我]有走她的孩子  艾莉
We didn't take her kids, Ellie.
是法庭了  有e忘了起因
The courts did. And don't forget why.
@些孩子之前生活得就像破屋里的野
Those kids were living like feral cats in a crack house.
我知道  我知道  但她看起磉是很正常的
I know, I know, but she kind of... She looks okay.
我的意思是  莎f她已四月]犯事了
I mean, Sharon said she's been clean for four months.
嗯  她]犯事  那是因樗坐^牢了啊  艾莉
Yeah, she got clean because she was in jail, Ellie.
看看看著她H的眼神
Look at the way Lizzy's looking at her.
她H是她H
She's still her mom.
我]有走她的孩子啊  艾莉
We didn't take her kids, Ellie.
那r我就f  @位年p女士
So I said, "Young lady,
如果我再一次f你在咖啡d里y扔食物
we hear about you throwing food in the cafeteria one more time,
你就多次和我一起吃午餐
and you're gonna have a couple of lunch dates."
第二天  她是y扔食物
Next day, the behavior continued.
所以我去了她的W校然后和她一起吃午
So we went to the school and joined her in the cafeteria.
和她所有的中W好朋友聊了天
Chattin' up all her middle school BFFs.
我跟他v了一些我最好的的^B故事
I walked them through some of my better bird-watching stories.
但他完全不感d趣
They were completely uninterested.
不^她就]有再y扔食物了
But that food throwing has stopped!
妙啊  妙啊
Good. Good.
你愿意分享一下你的故事
Would you like to share your news?
P于沙l著火的故事  不  P于你的二六
About the couch fire? No. About your .26 hearing.
二六  法庭Q定孩子法定Oo人的
嗯嗯
Yes.
法庭已依照法律
The court has legally cleared us...
把孩子判o我了
to adopt.
把娜和瑞安判o我了
To adopt Tina and Ryan!
太好啦  @真的太棒了
Yay! That is so great.
恭喜啊  我非常槟感到高d
Congratulations, guys. I'm so happy for you.
@真是非常好的一消息  我槟感到高d
That is such great news. I'm so happy for both of you.
那么下面有皮特和艾莉
And next we have Pete and Ellie.
好吧  你知道  我的孩子已
Well, you know, our kids have, what,
回去了他H四次了
had now four visits with their birth mom?
嗯哼  每一次他都非常
Yeah. And every time they do,
非常d^  特e在了他H后的那滋
they're just crazy for a few days after.
天哪
Holy...
他平o下砗  一切如常的r候
And just when things finally start to feel normal again,
他就再去他H
they have another visit.
嗯嗯  我感X被排D得很乐
Yeah, we just feel so rejected.
我也知道@可能你X得我很
And I know this probably makes me a really bad person,
但我真的一直希望他H能回去坐牢
but I just keep wishing that their mom would go back to prison.
你才不是娜四
You're not a bad person.
有人ξ心鄣暮⒆幼龀隹膳碌氖虑槭
When someone does terrible things to the children we love,
我很yδ人a生同情
it's not easy to find empathy for them.
但我是要M量去著同情
But we have to try, people.
ol生什么  孩子陪伴你的rg
Whatever happens, the time that your kids spent with you
已λ人生a生很大影  嗯哼
made a big difference in their lives. Mm-hmm.
嗯  我知道  但我就理去
Yeah, I know, but then we're just supposed to...
等等  你f已λa生影  Φ
Wait. Did you say "made" a difference? Yeah, she did.
我之后再
We-We'll talk after.
不 她f已  @是^去式  @就是不同
No. She said "made." That's past tense. There's a difference.
我想知道@是什么r  P
I wanna know what's going on, Karen.
好吧
Well...
b于的H已逐步_始c她的孩子重w于好
Since Lizzy's mom has been keeping up with her reunification steps,
法官把孩子判o你的事可能伊
the judge changed your .26 hearing to a Change of Circumstances hearing
法官Q定孩子是否跟回他H生活
where he'll decide if the kids are ready to reunite.
棒
Nice.
太棒了
Really nice.
@直就是
No, this is...
你打算[m著我
You weren't gonna share that with us?
我一直在和@破事杭mp
We've been dealing with all of this shit!
我是f  他yl脾  弄得家里一F糟  有那可怕的B度
I mean, the tantrums, the messes, the attitude.
我甚至已和塔玩了一百五十次糖果@
I have played 150 games of Candy Land with Lita.
糖果@  和棋子游
你玩^糖果世界
You ever play fricking Candy Land?
（俗：Candy Land一款m合幼旱暮钨游颍
太痛苦了  o聊透了
It's brutal! It's very dull.
我著和她多交流
We're making connections. Okay?
所以打算教塔WT自行
I mean I just taught Lita how to ride a bike.
阮和我在看《洛基 III》
Juan and I bonded over Rocky III.
（俗：Rocky III《洛奇III》由史泰拍z并主演的影）
F在就B也要胶瓦M砹
And now Mom's ready to reunite?
彼得  艾莉  我知道你很失望
Pete, Ellie, I understand your frustration.
但要知道我C的首要目司褪
But we all need to keep in mind that until the kids are adopted,
孩子受到家庭的庇o
the primary goal of the system is family preservation.
那又有l肀Ｗo我的家庭呢  l砟
And what about preserving our family? Yeah.
事情]有w棺定
Nothing has been decided yet.
那好  接下  W克托布
All right, October, that leaves you.
嗯 我也收B了一大孩子
Well, I have gotten a placement.
他14q了  ⒓恿松倌昊@球
Oh. He is 14 and does play JV basketball.
他身高有c低
But he is 5'2."
（俗：5'2'' 指最m合女性的身高）
皮w很白染著t^l
And white, with red hair.
也]什么基A
Absolutely no fundamentals whatsoever.
~  好吧  看起砦业}有c不合r宜
Oh, I get it. My problems seem stupid now.
槭裁次铱是最后一呢
Why do I always have to go last?
停下戆  -好的  我想f
Stop. Okay. I know. It's...
@很不I
It's very unprofessional.
@直就是互助小M的反例
This is the opposite of a support group.
我成什么幼
What am I gonna look like?
你看起硐漂亮的公主哦  哇
You're gonna look like a beautiful princess. Oh!
那我像花朵一用利
Do I look like a flower?
嘿  嘿  嘿  伙
Hey. Hey, hey, buddy.
-  嘿  孩子  -哦  嗨  H鄣
Mom. Hey, kids. Oh! Hi, honey!
嘿
Hey. Mom!
]事的 ]事的  它可以被洗掉的
No, no, no. It's totally washable.
可是  那是P
It's, um... That's a Sharpie.
（俗:SharpieP的一N，用水很y洗掉）
~  是的  ~  H鄣
Oh, yeah. Oh, dear.
H鄣  你能墓褡由舷  @很危U
Can you please get off the counter, honey? It's dangerous.
互助小M怎么  太有趣了
How was care group? So much fun.
嘿  嘿  嘿  我想告V你消息
Hey, hey, hey. We have news.
-你言辛  哦  天哪
You're pregnant? Oh, my God!
你槭裁催@么f  Σ黄  那是什么消息呢
Why are you doing this to me? I'm sorry. No?
快把消息告V他吧
It's okay. No. Just tell them.
_定
Yeah? Uh-huh.
R上  R上
Okay, okay.
我也打算通^寄B所眍IB孩子
We are going to adopt through foster care, just like you guys!
m然我不能言
I mean, we did not get it at first,
但是我遇到了你  看到了收B孩子@N方式
and then we met yours and saw what a wonderful choice it was.
比做管阂便宜的多了
Hell of a lot cheaper than in vitro too.
在@Q定中 你ξ的影挺大的
Which is not the reason, but it's a reason, if you're weighing factors.
所以我打算下周_始上n啦
And we start classes next week!
你X得怎么
What do you guys think?
我想  呃
I think, uh...
真是令人作I
I think I have to take a crap.
@好像不是我期待中的反
That's not the reaction we were looking for on that.
她一定是在嫉妒
She's jealous!
哦  嘿  哦  天哪  你在做什么
Oh! Hey! Oh, my God! What are you doing?
怎么了  把@o我  Lizzy
What's going on? Please give this to me. Lizzy!
你不能拿走我的手C  她在做什么
You're not allowed to take my phone! What's she doing?
天哪  她在浴室里拍裸照
God! She's taking naked selfies in the bathroom!
她在拍自己的裸照  e游业氖C
She's taking naked selfies of herself? What are you doing to my phone?
我要h除里面的所有热  全部h除
I'm deleting everything here! Delete, delete, delete.
你到底拍了多少  你到底槭裁催@么做
How many photos did you take? What is wrong with you?
大家都@么做  ]什么大不了的
Everyone does it! It's no big deal!
@很有}  @很重要
It's a big, huge, giant deal!
15q的女孩要自尊自
Fifteen-year-old girls should never be naked, ever!
你能拉著T  不能看我的短信  把T打_
Can you take the door? Don't read my texts! Open the door!
如果你不R上o我看照片  我可就]什么d趣了
"If you don't show me something soon, I might lose interest."
什么  @人是l    _T
What? Who is this person, Lizzy? Open the door!
哦  不  不  不  色情照  有色情照
Oh, no. No, no. Dick pic! There's a dick pic!
戆  孩子  我去客d呆著
Come on, kids, we are going in the living room.
你是在和一叫雅各布的人聊天
Is this that kid Jacob you were talking about?
那o你寄他性感照片的男孩
That sweet kid from school is sending you photos of his beeswax?
天哪  @可是老油l
Jesus, that is a trout!
（俗:Trout  指喜g20q年p女孩子的40q左右的男子）
x_@里
Get out of here!
F在快出
Lizzy! Get out here now!
把o我  放_
Give me the phone! Let go!
@并不r髦    我再也不想你f了
This is not cool Lizzy! I don't have to listen to you anymore,
你@假
Pretend Mom!
不是...
This isn't...
你猿诌@是一好的x
Still think it's a wonderful choice?
我的孩子不@么做的
Our foster kids aren't gonna act like that.
只是你的孩子而已
That's on you guys.
Dic pic是什么
What exactly is a dick pic?
你X得是什么呢    色情照啊
What do you think it is, Mom? Wild guess. Dick. Pic.
H鄣  我…面R@N}的r候
You know, honey, when I had... times like this,
我是不嗨伎
I had to search myself
并回
and remember...
一_始槭裁次疫x癯橐幻母H
why I became a mother in the first place.
@N思考很有椭
And that was helpful.
@是雅各布家  就是我要去的地方
Is this that kid Jacob's house? Is that where we're going?
冷oc  好  告V我咱在哪里
Just calm down, okay? Please tell me where we are.
我可不想被逮捕
I don't want to get arrested.
你只需要相信我就行  下吧
Will you just trust me? Come on.
哦  你好
Oh. Hi.
嘿  我不知道你是否得我
Hey. I don't know if you guys remember us.
寄B所^的的彼得和艾莉
Pete and Ellie from foster orientation?
哦  得  嗨  你好
Oh, yeah. Hi. How you doing?
呃  我能槟阕鲂┦裁茨
Uh, what can we do for you?
所以F在她想回碓僖淮纬橐晃荒赣H
So now she wants to come back and be Mommy again.
而且看起硭真的有C
And it looks like she's got a real shot.
她Υ我就像Υ橙艘
Lizzy, she's treating us like we're the enemy.
F在我不知道怎么k
Now we don't know what the hell to do.
所以我想知道槭裁茨的女喝绱秀
So I just thought, I mean, your daughter turned out so great.
她在那里W  嘿  布m_  你要下
Is she up there studying? Hey, Brenda, you gonna come down?
我想和她
I thought maybe we could speak with her,
也S能我像之前一颖в邢Ｍ
and she'd get us pumped up like before.
有可能  Φ  那太好了  她太棒了
Is that a possibility? Yeah, that'd be great. She was amazing.
我需要一次鼓舞人心的
We could use a pep talk right now.
嗯  布m_她  嗯…回到康椭行牧
Um, Brenda is, um... back in rehab.
Σ黄  什么  月前我lF她在吸毒
Excuse me, what? We caught her using a couple months ago.
你在跟我_玩笑
Are you shitting me right now?
她那鼓舞人心  令人心缟疋的演v
Her inspirational, heartwarming goddamn speech
是我初竺⒓踊拥闹饕原因
is the reason we signed up for this shit-show in the first place!
F在你告V我她又回了老幼印噢
Now you're telling me she's back on... Ow!
你我f  女人
You listen to me, crazy woman!
布m_一直在同毒品作斗
Brenda has struggled with substance abuse
她11q的r候被她母H的男朋友注射了冰毒
ever since her mother's boyfriend started her on meth when she was 11.
有r她走入歧途  但她是好孩子
Sometimes she stumbles. But she is a good kid.
她J真干活  把自己整理的干干
And she's in there doing the work, getting herself clean.
你不知道l生什么
So you don't know what's gonna happen.
所以你感到沮  害怕  失落
And this has you feeling what? Frustrated? Scared? Lost? Is that it?
我有c害怕  是的  ]e@就是
Yes! I'm a little afraid to say anything, but yes, that's basically
我的感受
how we feel.
@也正是你孩子每天的生活感受
That's how your children feel every day of their lives.
你IB他的r候  你自我感X良好
When you took this on, you felt good about yourself
因槟阒道@很重要  Π
because you knew that it mattered, right?
好吧  大家都知道的
Well, guess what.
重要的事情往往很困y
Things that matter are hard.
F在我知道布m_那
Now I know where Brenda
鼓舞人心的演v是哪睦淼撵`感了
gets her inspiring speech thing.
著  F在  你就是孩子的全部
Listen, guys, right now, you're all they've got.
所以你的工作就是保C他的安全
So your job is to keep them safe,
不他是否接受
whether they want you to or not.
他也被移默化的影了
He's got it too.
太不可思h了  xx您
That was incredible. Thank you.
很抱歉我δ愦蟀l脾
I'm so sorry that I blew up at you.
扇了你一巴掌
I'm sorry I slapped you!
]事  @很好  嗯  十分抱歉
I know! That was crazy! I know. I apologize.
@很好  我需要它  我好久]挨耳光了
It was good. I needed it. I haven't been slapped for a long time.
醍醐灌  茅塞D_
It was a bit aggressive. It was a little bit out of line.
可以可以  H鄣
Well, you were, honey. You were.
好吧  H鄣  我得走了
All right, honey, we gotta go.
我得走了  保重
We gotta get going. Take care.
xx您
Thank you.
在Facebook上能找到你Π  我P注你的
You're on Facebook, right? I'll find you. Okay!
再  再  xx您
Bye! Bye! Thank you!
再
Bye.
我快M屋吧  快c
Let's get in the house right away, really quick.
好的  你到啦  再
Okay, you're all set. Bye, Lizzy.
^得愉快哦
Have a great day.
接下  你把他送到W校
All right, look, you drop them off.
我找到@雅各布@小子  把事情搞清楚  好
I'm gonna find this Jacob kid and get to the bottom of this, okay?
好的  好的
Okay. All right.
等等  彼得  就是他  什么
Wait, Pete, that's him! What?
那拿著罐子的t^l男生
Him? That redhead kid right there? The kid with the soup can for a...?
戆  我要抓住他
Come on. I'm getting him.
你  猥男  嘿  嘿
You! Dick pic! Hey! Hey!
嘿 有事  伙  想翁
Hey! Excuse me. What's up, man? Wanted to catch a fade, huh?
猥男  bo辜
Dick pic! Think it's okay?
把你的小弟弟照片lo一15q的女孩
Sending pictures of your knob to a 15-year-old girl?
真幸\  我]有R上懒四  小}卜
You're lucky I don't end your life right now, carrot top.
我看到你o她的信：  如果你不睃c什么  我
I saw what you wrote to her: "If you don't show me something, I'm
失去d趣的
gonna lose interest."
那是性侵犯  年p人  真盒
That's actually sexual assault, young man. It's disgusting!
你不是大K^    秀一下
Not such a big man now, are you? Come on, whip it out!
大家看看你橹傲的大家伙
Show everybody those big shaved plums you're so proud of!
我要打o你  告V校L
We're gonna call your mom, tell the principal, maybe even call the
要缶
police.
你X得怎么  雅各布  我不是雅各布
What do you think of that, Jacob? My name's not Jacob!
什么  我叫查理
What? My name is Charlie.
他是查理
That's Charlie.
我以槟愦_定他就是雅各布  e了
I thought you said his name was Jacob. Really?
我的小弟弟]刮毛
And my plums aren't shaved.
他不大
Or big.
我很抱歉  哦  天哪  我很抱歉  H鄣
I'm so sorry. Oh, God. I'm so sorry, honey.
戆  伙  深呼吸  @是`
Come on, buddy, suck it up. It's a little snafu, okay?
戆  o我一肀  查理
Come on. Give me a hug, Charlie.
放松  看著我
All right, look at me.
你JR叫雅各布的人
Do you happen to know anybody named Jacob
l和我的女蝴在一起
who might be hanging around with our daughter, Lizzy Viara?
看T人  成人用品店的看T人
The janitor? The adult-ass janitor?
-我的天  走  我去找看T人
Oh, my God. Come on, let's get the janitor.
嘿  我很抱歉  艾莉  快c
Hey, I'm so sorry about this. Ellie, come on!
非常感x  和他oP
Thank you so much! He didn't do any of that.
快c  艾莉 和他]有一cP系
Come on, Ellie. He didn't do any of it!
快c  Σ黄  查理
Hurry up! I'm so sorry, Charlie!
我上W要t到了
I think we're gonna be late for school.
艾莉
Ellie
他在吃早  加油
He's on a Zamboni. Come on!
嘿  嘿  叫你呢
Hey! Hey, you!
嘿  我在和你f呢
Excuse me. I'm talking to you.
你多大了  你想知道什么
How old are you, Jump Street? Why you want to know?
-嘿  女士  把那我  那不是你的  他22q了
Hey, lady, gimme that. That's not yours. He's 22!
他22q  是的  我22q了  那又怎么
He's 22. Yeah, I'm 22. So what?
所以我不是在虐待和  彼得
So this won't be child abuse. Pete!
嘿  你之前碰^  想^  系^我女  要是再有下次
Hey, you ever touch, text, or think about our daughter ever again,
那你就死定了
and you're a dead man.
我要起V你  你不是她的H生父母
I'm gonna sue you, man! You're not even her parents!
她H生父母y道不@幼
Would not-her-parents do this?
佩佩小姐
Miss Peppers!
哇  哇  l生了什么
Whoa. Whoa. What's happening here?
他一直o我女喊l送淫xu和照片
This man has been sending lewd comments and photos to our daughter.
你今天要坐牢了  Jacob  你介意缶
You're going to jail today, Jacob! You mind calling the police?
必缶  佩佩小姐
Absolutely! Miss Peppers!
…
Mother...
xx  我很感激
All right. We appreciate it.
伙  我都]碰^那女孩
Man, I didn't even touch that girl.
L蛋吧  混蛋  盒牡偻癖
Bye-bye, scumbag. Filthy pedophile.
L去享受性侵犯者的生活
Yeah. Enjoy your life as a sex offender.
盒牡偻癖
Pedophile.
槭裁创捕我  那家伙把他的色情照
You're arresting us? The guy was sending pictures of his knob to a
lo了未成年
minor.
-你槭裁匆逮捕我  非常好  干得好
Why are you arresting us? Really good. Good work, guys.
必要f  我f了你的光x事E
For what it's worth, I heard what you guys did in there.
你是好父母  照你的孩子
You're good parents, looking out for your kids.
如果又C  我做同拥倪x瘛
If I'd had a chance to do the same...
孩子  哦  天哪
The kids! Oh, my God!
阮  塔  哦  天哪  真Σ黄  孩子
Juan, Lita! Oh, my God, I'm so sorry! Guys!
嘿  嘿
Hey. Hey, baby.
天哪  真干
My God, it's so clean.
嗯  我的小“匪徒”回砹
Well, there are my little gangsters.
保金交^了
Posting bail for my Petey.
我真的回到了^去的美好r光
Really took me back to the good old days.
xx  孩子在哪里
Thank you, by the way. Where are the kids?
P不得不把他У揭Rr的地方^夜
Karen had to take them to a temporary placement for the night.
她f@是她第一次fCPS在孩子C
She said it's the first time she's heard of CPS
的前一天晚上把他募酿B家庭ё
removing kids from their adoptive home the night before their hearing.
f到@  我看了你打印下淼年述~
Speaking of which, I found your statement to the judge on your printer.
需要M行一些修改
Needs some work.
太晚了  我上周已提交了
Mom, it's too late. We submitted it last week.
M管如此  是要重新提交一份
Well, resubmit it! Jesus!
“我要把最好的|西留o孩子
"We want whatever is best for the kids,
不管是和我在一起是回到H生母H身”
whether that means staying with us or returning to their birth mother. "
如果法官在利面前x到@句怎么k
What if the judge reads that crap in front of Lizzy?
@正是我下@句的原因
That's why we wrote it like that, Mom.
如果因殛述~е滤]有得到Oo
If she thinks our statement's the reason her mom doesn't get custody,
她比F在更恨我的
she's gonna hate us more than she does now.
她不恨你  她只X得你不鬯
She doesn't hate you. She just thinks you don't love her.
@份述~⒁o所用
And that statement ain't gonna help.
是和您f的  哦  并不是  Ellie
Did Lizzy tell you that? Oh, come on, Ellie.
我的成Lv和那孩子很像
I grew up a lot like that kid.
如果你每天都被人R你是屎
You get reminded what a sack of shit you are five times a day,
^了一  你直不敢相信有人勰
after a while, you can't believe anyone could ever love you.
你知道的我勰  Π
You know that we love you, right?
是的 我知道
No.
但不是你 我畚易约
But that's not you, it's me.
我以槲乙呀可以看淡所有
I thought I just covered all that.
但我真的勰
But I do love you both.
孩子  睡一X把
Get some sleep, kids.
在那之前e忘了改改述~
After you fix that god-awful statement.
真的
Wow.
@里既整又安o
It's so clean and quiet in here.
我知道
I know.
但我@
I hate it.
我也是
Me too.
-嘿  -嘿
Hey. Hey.
孩子  我很抱歉
Guys. We are so sorry.
我很抱歉  你]事吧
We are so sorry. Are you okay?
你知道  我坐著警^淼
Guess what? We got a ride in a police car.
是  有趣
You did? Was that fun?
你MOz了  是  我…就在Oz里
Did you guys go to prison? No. We were... just in jail.
阮  塔  ^戆
Juan. Lita. Come on.
在@里  好的
Mom's here. Okay.
好的  各位  26C是P于S拉
Okay, folks, our .26 hearing is now a Change of Circumstance hearing
小姐的情葑更
for a Miss Carla Viara.
-你是伊莎白 S拉小姐  是的  法官大人
And you are Miss Viara, yes? She is, Your Honor.
今天和我在一起的有阮  塔和伊莎白
And also with us today are Juan, Lita, and Elizabeth Viara?
在@里  在@里
Here. Here!
你都拿到泰迪熊了
And did you two each get a teddy bear?
是的  哦  它很漂亮
Yes! Oh, those are good ones.
-你是伊莎白  我是 先生
And you are Elizabeth? It's Lizzy, sir.
我是f  法官大人
I mean, Your Honor.
好的    我知道你已提交了一份明
And, Lizzy, I understand that you've submitted a statement.
寄B家庭父母f戈夫D也在
And the foster parents, Mr. And Mrs. Wagner, are they present as well?
是的  法官大人
Yes, Your Honor.
f戈夫D
And, Mr. And Mrs. Wagner,
你因乐匾u舳被捕r  你把阮和塔
is it accurate that you left Juan and Lita alone in your car
为留在了里
while you were being arrested for aggravated assault?
-嗯  那…是的  法官大人  但我是榱...
Well, that... Yes, Your Honor, but in our defense...
先生  我只P心Lizzy是不是撒e
Sir, all I need to know is whether or not Lizzy is lying.
她然]撒e
No, she's not lying.
在那次打糁前
And prior to that assault,
你在校@里和一14q的三好W生搭
did you accost a 14-year-old honor student in the same school yard
并鼓钏掏出他光滑的蛋蛋
and encourage him "to whip out his big, shaved plums"?
法官先生  我已f^了  并且
I said that, Your Honor, but again,
我X得是有人故意o她
I thought it was the person who sent her the...
Wagner夫人  你曾一度迫Lizzy的所有朋友
Mrs. Wagner, did you at one time force Lizzy's friends to leave your
x_你家
home
呐P室窗里爬出去x_
by way of a bedroom window?
那是一扇落地窗  那表P你了
It was a ground floor window. Good. Points for you.
同r你告VLizzy打叫CPS
And at that same occasion, did you tell Lizzy to call CPS and to come
把他都接走
and take the kids?
你`她了  我]想那么做
She didn't mean that. I did not mean that.
那次是在忸^上
That was in the heat of an argument.
法官先生  我有份情  我知道  看^了
Your Honor, I have a statement. Yes, I've read it, thank you.
我重了一份  女士  那  不用了吧
We actually wrote a new one. Ma'am, excuse me, but I have your...
拜托  法官大人  我]日]夜的心血在@
Please, Your Honor, we were up late working on it. I can read it very
我x的很快不耽`rg
fast.
Lizzy曾我槭裁词震B他
"Lizzy once asked us why we took them in.
我ro言以
And at the time, we couldn't answer her."
女士  你是坐吧  法官先生 允S我
Ma'am, please sit down. Please, Your Honor, can you let me say
您能允S我f出答案
the answer?
不用了  坐吧
No. Sit.
@雎Cc你oP
This hearing is not about you.
Lizzy的明砜  我在@地方面
Judging by Lizzy's statement, you might be back in court soon enough,
所以f@些留o日后f吧
so let's save that heartwarming speech for that occasion.
Viara小姐
Okay. Now, Miss Viara,
看砟阋恢痹诟M你的拜L  那很好
I see that you've been keeping up with your visits. That's good.
我也明白你^去五月一直很清醒
I also understand that you've been sober for the last five months.
F在是如此
Is that still the case?
是的  那可真是好消息了
Yes. That's very good news.
如果我你碚疹孩子
And if I were to put the kids in your care,
您家里住的下
your current residence could accommodate them?
那]}
I think so.
麻雀m小  五K俱全的 法官先生
It's small, but it works... Your Honor.
Viara小姐  你X得你能肩起P心e人的重任
And, Miss Viara, do you feel capable of responsibly caring
同r照Juan  Lita  Lizzy他三
for Juan, Lita, and Lizzy at this time?
Viara小姐
Miss Viara.
女士你在
Mama.
然  法官先生  ]}
Yes, Your Honor. I'm capable now.
所有人涑酝聿屠
Everybody get ready for dinner.
o你
Here you go.
如果以后和我一起住
What if when we go live with our mom,
她不知道怎么弄我鄢缘拿l花
she doesn't know how to make my noodles the way I like to have them?
伙e心  Lizzyo你做我做^的芝士
Don't worry, pal. Lizzy will show her the way we do the cheese for you
@幽不就做了
so your mom can make it for you just the way you like.
ε  e心啦
Yeah. Okay.
我一起的最后一晚啦  大家e垂^獾
Come on, guys. Don't be sad on our last night.
我X得我感xPete和Ellie
You know what? I think we should tell Pete and Ellie thank you,
他真的槲付出很多 不是
you know, for everything they've done for us, yeah?
xx你  我也要感x你 小家伙
Thank you. Well, thank you, pal.
xx大家
Yeah, thank you, guys.
Lita你呢  我不想f
Lita? I don't want to say anything.
怎么了
Oh, honey.
我去瞅一眼Lita
I'm just gonna go check on Lita.
我意思是  除非你想
I mean, unless you want to.
其我想fxx
Yeah, I would, actually. Thanks.
怎么了小家伙 你一勺都]
Come on, buddy. You haven't touched your pasta.
要不我o你在岚
You want me to reheat it for you?
]P系啦小家伙
It's okay, buddy.
不要y^  小家伙
That's okay, buddy.
好  小家伙  晚安啦
Good night, buddy. Good night.
晚安  我勰
Sweetie, good night. I love you.
我也勰
Love you too.
你所有的球鲂芏荚谶@里啦  包括那些新的
Okay, all your court bears are in here, the new ones as well.
f到@毫
Speaking of court, um,
很抱歉  我o法官的那些
I just wanted to apologize for what I wrote to the judge.
事如此
It was all true.
可能有c}  但是e往心里去
It was a little out of context maybe, but there's no hard feelings.
其我也好想o你我的那份明
Actually, I wanted to give you the statement we wrote
就是法庭上]Cx的那封 你看吧
that we couldn't read in court, just so you have it.
Yeah.
小家伙  砝
Guys, Mom's here.
收拾|西 涑霭l
All right. Get up! Come on. Let's go.
Lita  快去收拾你的|西
Lita, come on, get your stuff.
再咯  肉球
Bye, Meatball.
嗨  我oLita多Я座  怕你@]
Hey. I've got a car seat for Lita if you don't have one.
怎么是你斫游  呢
You guys picking us up? Where's Mom?
她今早和我在k公室碰面的
She was supposed to meet us at the office this morning
但她放子了
and she didn't show.
我的天
Oh, no.
她也不接
She didn't answer her phone.
你去她家看了  f一她出事了呢
Did you go to her house? What if something happened to her?
我然去看了  她很羞愧
Yes, we went to see her. She was very ashamed.
她f  她是做不到
She said... she can't do it.
我不相信  如果她不想  槭裁匆填那么多表
No, she didn't. Because why would she, um, fill out all the forms
M那么多事找法庭人TびH人T
and the court stuff and reunification stuff if she didn't...
Lizzy  你f你填完了所有表  我兔α
Lizzy, your mom said you filled out all those forms. I helped,
有呢
but so what?
她感X她在被逼著接受
She felt she was being pushed into something that she wasn't ready
她]浜玫氖
for.
并不是  ]有人逼她  她已浜昧
No. I didn't push her. She's ready!
我裾f吧
Just let me talk to her, please,
效果或S好一c
and then we can figure something out.
她本砟我回家的
Honey. And she can take me home.
H鄣  我看到她第一眼就明白了
Honey, when we saw her, it was obvious.
她又重蹈覆H了
She's using again.
她不砹
She's not coming, baby.
很抱歉
Sweetie, we're so sorry.
Lizzy
Lizzy.
我去找她  你留下看好孩子
I'll go get her. You watch the kids.
在@里等我 好不好  Lizzy
Just wait there, okay? Lizzy!
Lizzy
Lizzy!
Lizzy  Lizzy
Lizzy? Lizzy!
Lizzy  不要管我了  你又不是我H生父母
Lizzy. Please just go away. You're not my parents.
是  你f得  但我永h陪伴你
No, we're not. But you know what we are? We're here.
我一直在你身  用心去勰
That's right, we're here and we love you.
怎么可能  你真的懂我
What? No, you don't. You don't even know me.
@怎么了
Hey, what the hell's going on out here?
您能我为呆
Could you just give us a few minutes, please?
]}  不好意思啊
Oh, okay. Sorry.
Lizzy  H鄣  我然懂你
Lizzy, honey, we do know you.
比如你芝士
We... We know that you hate cheese,
但你又超喜g芝士h堡
but you really love cheeseburgers.
我知道  早上你要是心情好了
And we know that when you feel good in the morning,
你化的y比心情不好r淡一cc
you put on a little less makeup than you do on the bad days.
]e吧  而且我知道  δ碚f
Exactly. And we know that the most important thing in the world to you
世上最重要的事是保o好Juan和Lita
is to protect Juan and Lita from the things nobody protected you from.
我f的  是不是
We know that about you, right? Yes, honey.
你做的很棒了
You guys are doing good.
-Σ黄  -我知道有很多我不了解的事
I'm sorry. We know there's so much we don't know.
但如果你害怕我南息
But if you're afraid we can't handle knowing the bad stuff, or the
或可怕的事物理不好
scary stuff,
我做得很好  我保C
we can, I promise.
е@承Z  不管l生什么 一起面
Yeah, bring it. Whatever you got, we want it.
因槲勰  Lizzy
Because we love you, Lizzy.
求你ef了  走吧
Stop saying that. Please just go away, please.
走吧
Please.
Lizzy好  小家伙  她F在有c
Is Lizzy okay? She's a little upset right now, buddy.
那你好  我]事
Are you okay? Yeah, I'm good.
看看l砹
Here she is.
所以…
So...
我是X得@鹤詈
um, here's what I think is best.
你陷入@件事的r候
I know Juan and Lita are more like what you had in mind when you got
你的X子里只有Juan和Lita
into this.
^
Come on, baby.
我X得最好是你收B他
So I think the best thing is for you to adopt them.
有  我Kareno我重新找地方
And... And I'll just ask Karen for, um, a different placement.
所以  e@
So... No.
]事  @幼詈  不  一c都不好
No, it'll be good. No, honey.
我需要你Juan和Lita呢
We need your help with Juan and Lita.
]有你我可做不到
We're not doing this without you.
需要兔α穗Sr系我 我常
I'll visit all the time and you can call me if you need help for
在家看看
anything.
不可能  Pete  我F在真不想檫@吵
No. Pete, I really don't want to argue about this right now.
我不管  我f^那不可能  明白
I don't care. I said no. That's not happening, okay?
你和我在一起
You're with us now. Yeah.
你明白  我X得冥冥之中自有天意
And you know why? We've got a cosmic connection.
我X得冥冥之中自有天意
That's right, we've got a cosmic connection.
我知道你F在可z我  你不用@
I know you feel sorry for me right now, but you really don't have to..
和l生的一切都oP
It's got nothing to do with what just happened.
Ellieo你的法庭述呢
Where's the court statement Ellie gave you?
看到]  大x
See this? Read that.
Lizzy曾我槭裁次收B他
"Lizzy once asked me why we did this, why we took them in.
那r我o不了她答案
We couldn't give her an answer at the time.
@么做是因槲感X生命中e^了什么
We did it because something was missing in our lives, but we didn't
我又然不知
know what it was.
原砭褪悄
It was Juan, Lita, and Lizzy."
明白了
You see?
你就是我缺少的那一K
You were what was missing, Lizzy.
F在既然我在一起了
But now you're here and you are stuck with us.
Π  我要出F在每球鲇蛑
That's right. We're gonna be at every soccer game.
我δ愕某煽火冒三丈
We're gonna be all over your ass about your grades.
我要o你I人生第一件舞Y服
We're gonna buy you your first prom dress.
一定超好看的  既可塾植暴露太多
It's gonna be really pretty. But not too revealing. Super sweet.
就那N不很性感的
You know, not too sexy.
就像  你是最甜美的那
Just like... really, that gorgeous sweet spot.
ε  你高中I了
Yeah. And when you graduate high school,
我在前排v你的糗事
we're gonna be in the front row embarrassing you.
你大WI的r候  我那么干
We're gonna be in the front row again when you graduate college, or
或者不上都成
even if you don't.
你一定大WI  你那么明
You will be graduating college, 'cause it's so important and you're
δ碚f很重要
so smart.
我不逼你  但是大WIC遇更多
I don't mean to push, but it just opens up so many more opportunities.
但不如何  我都伴你左右
But either way, we're gonna be there for you.
直到某天  我在你的婚Y上送e你
And someday I'm gonna give you away at your wedding.
即使我J樗是笨蛋  他也不配
Even if I think the guy's a pissant and he's not good enough for my
我家小姑娘
little girl.
多好啊  砟程
That's right. Someday in the future.
bh而|不可及的未
Someday in the way, way, way off, deep, deep, deep distant future.
lizzy  我回家吧
Lizzy, can we go home now?
我也@酉氲
Yeah, I guess we can.
我知道你不喜g@
I know you don't like this,
但你偶也要T一下  好不好
but you're gonna have to get used to it once in a while, okay?
我能硪嘛  自奈艺JR你
Can I get one? I haven't gotten a single hug from you since I've
我一都]抱^
known you.
o面子吧
Please?
嗨  我m然不明白l生什么了
Hi. I don't know the whole context of everything.
但我只想知道我能不能也抱一下下
But I'm just wondering if I can just get in on that hug a little bit.
不用不用  心I了  xx您
We're good! Thank you so much. We're good, thank you.
Σ黄  我不@拥  你^m
Sorry. That was just wrong. Yeah, I just do that. You guys hug.
我有c^了
I crossed a boundary there.
一切也都好起淼
Everything's gonna work out great too.
我敢保C
I can tell.
嗨
Hi!
喔  太感x了
Oh! Oh, thank you!
再咯  回
Bye. Bye!
你一起  你JR他
Are you with them? Do you know those guys?
JR啊  怎么了
Yeah. Why?
你想M碜坐
Do you guys want to come in?
我  我做了岷醯呐
Uh... I-I made a pie.
不用了  xx  必去了
No, thank you. Yes!
Karen  那可是派啊  你不了解我
Karen! It's pie. You know I love pie.
太好了 真的 我想法太多了F在
Great. Yeah, I just... I have so many feelings.
上所  穿上鞋  我出l了  好
Go potty, put your shoes on. We're gonna go, okay?
好}
Okay!
Juan  哥  你干嘛呢
Whoa, Juan. What are you doing, buddy?
可不能穿\有  今天我得看起砜
You can't wear sneakers. We gotta look good today.
老你我手C了
Mom, have you seen my phone?
]啊 你意思是你手上那是吧
Uh, no. Wait, you mean the one in your hand?
Lita  小  你上^所了
Lita, honey, did you go potty?
我去^啦  非常棒
I went potty! Okay, good job.
全部上所去  我去^啦
Everybody go potty! Yeah, I went potty.
上我要У陌裹了  -是的  都浜昧
Got that packet we're supposed to bring? Yeah, I'm all set.
出l咯  出l
Let's go, guys. Let's go.
我要A咯
I'm gonna beat you!
然不行
No, no, no.
Ｐ拈_  行吧
No distracted driving, okay?
]}  _定
All right. All right?
她黹_  真的呀
She's gonna drive. Oh, yeah?
是的  我拿著手C坐前排
Yes, but I have the phone and I'll sit in the front
以防我不得不抓方向P或者停  好
in case I have to grab the wheel or shut down the power, okay?
Sandy  快c快c  要_始啦
Sandy, come on, it's started!
我]t到吧  好
Did I make it? Yeah, yeah, yeah.
那是啥啊
What's that?
Lizzyo我做的  你]有
Lizzy made it for me. You didn't get one?
你居然得到了一短袖
You got a T-shirt? You got a T-shirt?
T位就座
You may all be seated.
大家早上好
Good morning, folks.
所周知  家庭法庭很重要…
You know, family court is important...
稍等一下  等等  等等
Wait. Wait! Wait! Wait.
Sandy奶奶就座完  可以_始啦
Grandma Sandy's in the house. We can begin.
我f的]e吧  e[
Told you we'd make it. Stop it!
-@些座被占了  Π  就是o我占的
These seats are saved. Yeah, they're saved for me.
往^挪  e[啦
Move over. Stop it!
法官先生您^m  感x配合  洛尼特奶奶
Go ahead, Judge. Thank you, Grandma Sandy.
居然送她短袖
She got a T-shirt.
所周知 家庭法庭意x重大
You know, family court is important work.
但是做好也不容易
But it's difficult work.
我日鸵蝗盏靥理一些事情
We spend day in and day out dealing with things
理我X得大家不面Φ氖虑
that we feel no family should have to go through.
所以在@y得的滋炖  我笑起r
So on these rare days when we get to smile at work,
意味著@些任AM完成
these days mean a great deal to all of us.
我或S看不到  但我很多愁善感
And I may not look it, but I'm a huge cornball
我以此而活
and I live for this.
Ronit
Ronit?
我懂
Yeah!
我超圻@歌
I love this song.
今天大家共聚一起斫M建新家庭
We are here today to officially create a new family.
Elinore  Wagner和Peter
Peter and Elinore Wagner,
今天你Q定好要和Juan Lita Lizzy成橐患胰肆
do you wish to adopt Juan, Lita, and Lizzy into your family today?
毫o疑 法官先生
Yes, Your Honor. Yes, Your Honor.
@歌的我多愁善感的
It's just the song that's got me a little emotional.
Juan  Lita  和Lizzy
Juan, Lita, and Lizzy,
你愿意做Elinore  Wagner和Peter的孩子
would you like Peter and Elinore to be your mom and dad?
我愿意
Sure.
毫o疑  那必的呀
Yes, please. Yes!
b于此
Well, then,
按照法以及加州x予我的嗔
by the authority vested in me by the state of California,
我宣布你正式成橐患胰
I pronounce you a family.
o您  太感x了
Here you go. Thank you.
要和法官合影  那然了
Would you like to take a picture with the judge? Yeah, sure.
xx
Thank you.
戆
Yeah, let's do it.
R上我啦
That's gonna be us soon.
有我呢  我也是@家的啊
Oh, I'm part of this family too.
哈哈 感x您  有我呢
Okay, thank you. Wait, me too!
我也想^去拍 你_定  我]
I'd like to be in the picture. Are you sure? We're not...
我一起去  他一定也愿意
We should all go. I think they'd like that.
那就走
Okay. Okay. Yeah.
各就位啦
Okay! Okay.
都到R了
Anybody else?
有你呢  快一起
Yeah, you too. Come on!
@下AM啦
Okay, I think that's everybody.
喊 全家福  全家福
Say "Family." Family!
HDZIMU中文字幕W http://www.hdzimu.com
本站字幕H供翻gW交流,禁止用于商I用途
最新衢T影字幕P注新浪微博:HDZIMU中文字幕W
本站提供o需打_W站就能自酉螺d影字幕的件，g迎下d使用